This is a carousel with auto-rotating slides. Use Next and Previous buttons to navigate.

Holiday shopping = check! Take up to 30% off select products. [Terms apply](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Promotions).

[**Bundles**](https://naturesway.com/collections/bundle-save) have landed! Shop curated collections of your favorite products. 

[**Sign up**](#signup) for our mailing list for 20% off your first order. Terms apply.

Nature's Way

* Shop All
    
    Shop All
    
    * CATEGORIES

    * FEATURED

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* Health Interests
    
    Health Interests
    
    * CATEGORIES

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* Learn
    
    Learn
    
    * THE WELLNESS COLLECTIVE

    * EDUCATION

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* About
    
    About
    
    * WHO WE ARE

    * OUR BRANDS

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")

* [Wishlist](javascript:closeHeaderDrawer())

* Shop All
    
    CATEGORIES

    FEATURED

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* Health Interests
    
    CATEGORIES

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* Learn
    
    THE WELLNESS COLLECTIVE

    EDUCATION

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")
    
* About
    
    WHO WE ARE

    OUR BRANDS

    [
    
    #### Subscribe & Save
    
    Get 15% off your essentials.](https://naturesway.com/collections/subscribe-save "Subscribe & Save")[
    
    #### Weight Wellness\*
    
    Start your journey now.](https://naturesway.com/pages/weight-management-journey "Weight Wellness*")

[](#)[](https://naturesway.com/account)[](javascript: void(0))[Cart](https://naturesway.com/cart)

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Free shipping on US orders $35+ Spend $35.0 to get free shipping! 

My Wishlist ()
--------------

Legal
=====

#### Privacy Policy

Nature’s Way - Website Privacy Policy  
  
Last Modified: November 11, 2024

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites, social media pages, mobile applications, or online services that are owned or controlled by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Nature’s Way,” “our,” “we,” or “us”) and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Sites,” and individually, a “Site”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Sites and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Nature’s Way (unless specifically stated). This Privacy Policy describes our information collection and use practices, as well as rights you may have with respect to the personal information we collect.  
  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website owned or operated by any third party even if such third party links to a Site or if Nature’s Way links to that third-party website. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any third party or business partner that Nature’s Way does not own or control. Your use of this website is also governed by our [Terms of Service](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Terms%20of%20Service). Please review this Policy and our Terms before using the Sites. By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, do not access or use the Sites.

**NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**  
  
California Notice at Collection  
  
We collect Personal Information as detailed here and in our Privacy Policy. The following serves as our notice at collection of Personal Information in accordance with California law. As defined by applicable law, we may “sell” or “share” certain Personal Information. If you would like to opt out of the sale or sharing of your Personal Information, you may do so [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963). You may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”). We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt out.  
  
We keep Personal Information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also keep Personal Information as otherwise required by law. What this means in practice will vary between different types of information, and when we consider our approach we take into account ongoing business or legal needs for the information, for example in relation to tax, health and safety, and potential or actual disputes or investigations.  
  
We collect your Personal Information as disclosed in the “Collection of Information Section” below.  
  
**1\. DEFINITIONS**  
  
For purposes of this Privacy Policy:  
  
“Aggregate or De-Identified Information” means information about groups or categories of data, which does not identify and cannot reasonably be used to identify an individual.  
  
“Cookies” means unique identifiers that a website places on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device when you visit the website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its Privacy Policy.  
  
“Flash Cookies” means local shared objects that are used to store personalized information based on visits to websites.  
  
“Personal Information” means information that identifies or is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household, such as the individual’s name, postal address, email address or telephone number.  
  
“Web Beacons” means small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its Privacy Policy.  
  
**2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
  
We collect information in different ways. We collect information listed in the “What Categories of Information we Collect About You” section below when you provide us that information voluntarily. For example, if you register an account with us, contact us for information, or participate in a promotion.  
  
We also collect information about you automatically. Where permitted by law we use tracking tools such as browser Cookies and Web Beacons to collect information from you. We collect information about users over time when you use the Sites. We collect information about you from third parties, such as social media platforms and advertising analytics providers. We may have third parties collect information as described in this Privacy Policy, for example in Section 6.  
  
We may collect information about you from third parties and commercially-available sources, including from social media providers, survey providers, data aggregators, data brokers, and public or commercially-available databases. We may collect information about your interactions with our ads on third-party sites. We may also collect information about you from our service providers, affiliates, and business partners.  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| What categories of Personal Information do we collect? | What are the purposes for which we collect and use your Personal Information? |
| * _Identifiers_: This includes your real name, postal address, Internet Protocol address, telephone number, email address, or other similar identifiers.<br>* _Characteristics of Protected Classifications:_ This includes your age, race, color, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), medical condition, physical or mental disability, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, marital status, veteran or military status, and genetic information (including familial genetic information).<br>* _Commercial Information:_ This includes records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.<br>* _Internet or other Electronic Network Activity Information:_ This includes browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.<br>* _Geolocation Data:_ This includes physical location or movements.<br>* _Audio Information:_ This includes data relating to call transcripts with Nature’s Way personnel.<br>* _Professional or employment-related information:_ This includes information related to your employment and employment history.<br>* _Inferences Drawn from Above:_ This includes a profile reflecting a person’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | * We use information to respond to your requests or questions.<br>* We use information to improve our Sites, products, programs and services.<br>* We might use your information to customize your experience with us.<br>* We use information to administer our Site and for internal operations. For example, we may aggregate or de-identify your information for analytics, research or other business purposes. We combine information. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online, to the extent permitted by law, for the transactional purpose, or by your consent. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.<br>* We use information for security purposes. Where legally permitted, we may use your information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.<br>* We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products or services or special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about our products, services and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll send you our promotional emails.<br>* We use information to communicate with you about your account, purchases or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or for feedback. We might also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Site Usage Terms of Service.<br>* We use information to comply with applicable law, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law. |

**3\. USE OF INFORMATION**  
  
We may use the information we collect from and about you for a variety of business and commercial purposes, including:  
  
**Fulfilling your Request.** We use information that we collect including Personal Information for a variety of purposes. We use information to respond to your requests or questions, or to complete a transaction. We use information to improve our Sites, products, programs and services. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.  
  
**To Provide our Sites**. We use information to administer our Site and for internal operations. For example, we may aggregate or de-identify your information for analytics, research or other business purposes. We combine information. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.  
  
**Security and Fraud Prevention**. We use information for security purposes. Where legally permitted, we may use your information to protect our Company, our customers, and our Sites.  
  
**Targeted Advertising.** We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products or services or special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about our products, services and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll send you our promotional emails.  
  
**Providing You with Personalized Recommendations.** If you choose to complete assessments in the Services, we will use information that you provide to send you personalized product recommendations and other information that we believe may be of interest to you. We also use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertising and content, and to allow you to participate in interactive features, when you choose to do so. For example, we remember your login ID/email address or screen name so that you can quickly login the next time you visit the Services or so that you can easily retrieve the items you previously placed in your shopping cart.  
  
**Third-Party Social Networks**. We use your Personal Information when you interact with third-party social networking features, such as “Like” functions, to serve you with advertisements and engage with you on third-party social networks. You can learn more about how these features work and the profile data that we obtain about you, and find out how to opt out by reviewing the privacy notices of the relevant third-party social networks.  
  
**Performing Analyses**. We use your Personal Information to perform business analyses or for other purposes designed to improve the quality of our business and the Services we offer.  
  
**Preventing and Detecting Fraud and Other Crimes**. We use your Personal Information to help prevent and detect fraud and other crimes that might be committed using or against the Services. We may use your Personal Information to investigate possible violations of and enforce our contracts. We may also use your Personal Information to protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates. We do this to protect our business assets and to comply with our legal obligations.  
  
**Managing and Operating Our IT Systems**. We use your Personal Information to help us in troubleshooting, testing, maintaining, and protecting our IT systems, including our Sites.  
  
**Complying with Legal and Regulatory Obligations**. We use your Personal Information to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, which arise from time to time. For instance, we may use your contact information to alert you if a product is recalled.  
  
**Communicating with You.** We use information to communicate with you about your account, purchases or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or for feedback. We might also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Site Usage Terms of Service.  
  
We use information to comply with applicable law, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law.  
  
**4\. DISCLOSURE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION.**  
  
**Affiliates.** We are affiliated with a number of other health and wellness brands (collectively, our “Affiliates”). We may share your Personal Information with our Affiliates to send you promotions, information about sales and offers, and newsletters in which you have indicated interest and for legal and other business purposes.  
  
**Business Partners.** We may share your Personal Information with companies with whom we partner to offer goods or services (e.g., joint products or promotions).  
  
**Service Providers**. We may use third party service providers to perform certain services on behalf of the Sites, such as web site hosting, accepting job applications, providing web site usage analytics, sending email or other communications, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, providing consumer affairs services, fulfilling and processing orders, or performing other administrative services. Some of these service providers may collect information on the Sites directly from you on our behalf; in such cases, these service providers are not permitted to use your Personal Information for their own use.  
  
**Analytics and Advertising Partners.** You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from one or more third parties. If you agree at that time to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to that third party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties. You also may request, sometimes through your use of an interactive feature or third party application, that we share information about you with a third party, and we will typically do so under those circumstances.  
  
**Sponsors or Administrators.** We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (collectively, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list.  
  
We may also disclose your Personal Information: i) as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; ii) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a valid government request; or iii) if Nature’s Way is involved in a merger, acquisition, assignment, divestiture, bankruptcy, consolidation, reorganization, liquidation, transfer or sale of all or a portion of its assets.  
  
**5\. COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**  
  
We collect information, and authorize our third party vendors to collect information, about users over time across our Sites and for other services. To do this, we and/or our third party vendors use several common tracking tools. These may include Cookies, Web Beacons, Flash Cookies, and similar technologies.  
  
In connection with an email delivery and marketing company to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email messages and at our Site to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, how our visitors use our Site and to enable us to provide more focused and subsequent email marketing communications to you.  
  
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Sites are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with Web Beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content, which is often referred to as remarketing.  
  
While we may use a variety of service providers to perform advertising services, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.aspopens in a new tab, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/opens in a new tab, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an “opt-out” by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. Please note that these companies may still collect information when you are online and opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while visiting the Sites and elsewhere online.  
  
**6\. SECURITY AND RETENTION**  
  
Nature’s Way has reasonable technical and organizational security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of Personal Information under our control. However, given the nature of technology, we cannot guarantee that our systems are 100% secure. We periodically update our technology in order to improve the protection of customer information.  
  
We retain Personal Information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also keep Personal Information as otherwise required or permitted by law.  
  
**7\. WE STORE INFORMATION BOTH IN AND OUTSIDE OF THE U.S.**  
  
Personal Information we collect from you may be transferred to, or stored at, a destination in the United States or another destination outside of United States. It may be processed by staff operating in these locations who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your Personal Information to the United States. U.S. laws may not afford the same level or protection as those in your country.  
  
**8\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**  
  
Nature’s Way may make changes to this statement from time to time. We will post changes to our Privacy Policy here, so be sure to check back periodically.  
  
**9\. UNSUBSCRIBING FROM MARKETING MESSAGES**  
  
You may unsubscribe from receiving offers and promotions for our products and services through the unsubscribe mechanisms provided in our promotional communications. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.  
  
**10\. OUR SITES AND CHILDREN**  
  
Our Sites are meant for adults, and are not directed at children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 18 has given us information, you can contact us at privacyquestion@naturesway.com, or write to us at Customer Care at 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."  
  
**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
  
**Explanation of Applicable Privacy Rights**  
  
If you are a California, Virginia, Colorado or Connecticut resident, you may take advantage of the following privacy rights:  

* **Right to Know**: You have the right to request that we provide you with what Personal Information we have collected about you, including the categories of Personal Information, the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information, or for Virginians, what Personal Information is used for targeted advertising, the categories of third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information, and the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you. You have the right to receive this information in a portable format.

* **Right to Delete:** You have the right to request that we delete Personal Information that we have collected from you, subject to certain exceptions. Note that there are some reasons we will not be able to fully address your request, such as if we need to complete a transaction for you, to detect and protect against fraudulent and illegal activity, to exercise our rights, for our internal purposes, or to comply with a legal obligation.

* **Right to Correct:** You have the right to request that we correct inaccurate Personal Information that we may maintain about you, subject to appropriate verification.

* **Right to Opt-Out of the Sale or Sharing of, or Targeted Advertising using, Personal Information:** You may have the right to opt-out of the "sale" or "sharing" of, or targeted advertising using, your Personal Information, as such terms are defined by applicable state privacy laws, to third parties, which may include our affiliated companies that do not share the same brand name. This means that, if you opt out, going forward, we will not sell or share your Personal Information with such third parties to use for their purposes, including, as applicable, for targeted advertising and cross-context behavioral advertising, unless you later direct us to do so.

* **Right to Limit:** You have the right to request that we limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive personal information.

* **Right to Appeal:** Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut residents also have the right to appeal a denial of their privacy rights.

**How to Submit a Request**  
  
For California, Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut residents, to take advantage of your right to know/access, delete, correct, or portability, or to submit an appeal of a denial of your privacy rights under Virginia, Colorado, or Connecticut law, please click [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963) or contact us by email at privacyquestion@naturesway.com, or by using the “Contact Us” section below. If by email, please indicate the type of request you are making in the subject line of your message. We may request certain information to verify your identity before we can respond to such requests. We will confirm receipt of your request within ten (10) business days and will respond to your request within forty-five (45) calendar days, after proper verification, unless we need additional time, in which case we will let you know.  
  
To take advantage of your right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of Personal Information or to opt-out of targeted advertising, please click on the [Do Not Sell or Share My Data](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Do%20Not%20Sell%20or%20Share%20My%20Data "Nature's Way Privacy Requests") link which also is on our site footer or contact us using the “Contact Us” section below. We will work to comply with your opt-out request within 15 business days.  
  
California, Connecticut, and Colorado residents may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal opt-out preference via a tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”). We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt out.  
  
We will not discriminate against you because you exercised your rights under this section of the Privacy Policy.  
  
**Agent Requests**  
  
You may authorize someone to make a privacy rights request on your behalf (an authorized agent). Authorized agents will need to demonstrate that you’ve authorized them to act on your behalf or must demonstrate they have power of attorney pursuant to applicable probate law. We retain the right to request confirmation directly from you confirming that the agent is authorized to make such a request, or to request additional information to confirm the agent’s identity. An authorized agent is prohibited from using a consumer’s Personal Information, or any information collected from or about the consumer, for any purpose other than to fulfill the consumer’s requests, for verification, or for fraud prevention. If you are making a request as an authorized agent, please contact us using the information in the “Contact Us” section below, and provide your full name, address, email address, the full name of the person on whose behalf you are making the request, their address, email, phone number, as well as the written permission of the person on whose behalf you are acting to do so.  
  
**Specific Data Protection Disclosures**  
  
Personal Information We Collect  
  
We have collected the categories of Personal Information disclosed in the “Notice to California Residents” section above, including within the last twelve (12) months.  
  
We Obtain the Categories of Personal Information Listed Above From the Following Categories of Sources:  

* Directly from you. For example, when you sign up for email on our Site.
* From other sources, such as marketing partners, social events, and social networking sites.
* Automatically through the use tracking technologies, as disclosed in the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section.

We collect Personal Information for the business and commercial purposes described in the “Use of Information” section above.  
  
Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for Business Purposes: We may disclose your Personal Information to a third party for a business purpose. When we disclose Personal Information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that Personal Information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.  
  
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the categories of Personal Information listed in the “Notice to California Residents” section above, for a business purpose.  
  
We disclose your Personal Information for the business purposes disclosed above in “Use of Information” to the following categories of third parties:  

* Our Affiliates.

* Service providers. We engage certain third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

Categories of Personal Information Sold or Shared  
  
Each category of Personal Information disclosed in “Personal Information We Collect” was sold or shared with analytics and advertising partners, business partners, advertising networks, advertising platforms, social media companies, and third parties, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy within the last 12 months, including for targeted advertising. We do not knowingly sell or share Personal Information about persons under the age of 16.

#### Terms of Service

Schwabe North America, Inc. - Website Terms of Service Agreement

_Date Last Modified: November 11, 2024_

Schwabe North America and its subsidiaries and affiliates, including Nature’s Way Brands, LLC, ("Schwabe North America,” “we,” “our” or “us”) welcome you. The following Website Terms of Service Agreement ("Site Terms of Service") governs your use of this Internet website owned and operated by Schwabe North America (the "Site"). Please read these Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy carefully because they govern your use of the Site and our online store for our Products. The Site is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained in these Site Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy. For ease of reference, the Site and our online store are collectively called the “Services.”  

1. **Agreement to Site Terms of Service**

By accessing and using the Services, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions contained in these Site Terms of Service, you acknowledge: (i) that we will process your information; and (ii) to the use of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with our Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms set out in these Site Terms of Service, you must not use the Services.

2. **Your Obligations**

You are required to comply with all applicable laws in connection with your use of the Services, and such further limitations as may be set forth in any written or on-screen notice from Schwabe North America. As a condition of your use of the Services, you warrant that you will not use the Services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Site Terms of Service.

3. **Privacy Policy**

You agree and consent to the terms of the Schwabe North America Online Privacy Policy, a copy of which you should review by clicking [here](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20Policy).

4. **Availability of the Services**

We make no representations and provide no warranties that: (i) the Services will be made available at any time or from any specific geographical location; (ii) your access to the Services will be continuous or uninterrupted; or (iii) the Services will be accessible or optimized on all browser, computers, tablets, phones or viewing platforms.  We reserve the right to suspend access to all or part of the Services for any reason, including for business or operational reasons, such as improving the appearance or functionality of the Services, content updates, periodic maintenance, or to resolve any issues of which we become aware. The Services are provided for users in the United States. Although it may be possible to access the Services from other countries, we make no representation that the Services are compliant with any legal requirements in force in any jurisdiction other than United States, or that the content available on the Site will be appropriate for users in other countries.

5. **No Professional Advice**

Any information supplied through the Services or by any employee or agent of Schwabe North America, whether by telephone, e-mail, letter, facsimile or other form of communication, is for educational purposes or general guidance on the use of the Services, and does not constitute medical, legal, tax, accounting or other professional advice. Health-related information provided through the Services is not a substitute for medical advice and it is important that you not make medical decisions without first consulting your personal physician or health care practitioner. The information provided through the Services and on the Site does not replace the relationship that exists between you and your physician. **You should not use the information on this site for diagnosing or treating a health problem or disease**. Under no circumstances will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the Site.  The receipt of any questions or feedback you submit to Schwabe North America does not create a professional relationship and does not create any confidentiality privileges beyond those described in our Privacy Policy.  

6. **Online Product Purchases**

(a) Product Purchases. You may purchase products available on the Site. All products, specifications, descriptions, and prices are subject to change at any time without notice. Your purchase is subject to these Site Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to refuse any order you place with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order.  In the event that we make a change to or cancel an order, we may attempt to notify you by contacting the e-mail and/or billing address/phone number provided at the time the order was made.  

(b) Payment Information. You will be asked to enter your payment details during the checkout process. By placing an order, you confirm that the credit card you use is yours. All card payments are subject to authorization by your card issuer.

(c) Express Checkout. In addition, you can select an express check option: Shop Pay, Google Pay, or Apple Pay. When any of these payment options are selected, you are using that tool to manage payment, billing address, and shipping address.

(d) Shipping. Products you purchase through the Site will be shipped to you at the address you designate as the shipping address during the check-out process. We are not responsible for any packages that are refused or held for delivery. Refunds will not be issued for any orders that are refused by intended recipient or that cannot be delivered to due to an address error.  Currently, our Products are only available for purchase by residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia, and will only be shipped within the 50 United States and the District of Columbia. Free ground shipping on all orders of $35 or more. Some products may not be available to ship to some states due to applicable state laws.

(e) Return Policy. If you are not satisfied with your purchase for any reason, you may return it within 45 days of the date of your purchase for a full refund, excluding any shipping charges.  Please keep your packing slip or confirmation email for proof of purchase. We monitor return activity for abuse and reserve the right to limit or refuse returns or exchanges.

We reserve the right to request the product be shipped back to us in its original packaging at the customer’s expense and we do not assume responsibility for lost or misdirected returns. Please note that clearance items, as well as short-dated and expired product are not eligible for an exchange or refund.

7. **Subscribe & Save**

When you purchase a subscription you will regularly receive repeat deliveries. These are based on the subscription duration and frequency that you select. Your recurring subscription(s) will remain active until either you or Nature’s Way decides to cancel. You or Nature’s Way can terminate any recurring subscription at any time, and there will be no cancellation fee or ongoing charges after cancellation, except if a shipment in a recurring subscription has already been processed before cancellation. In such a case, the recurring subscription shipment will be canceled after that specific shipment, and you will be responsible for the payment of the last shipment.

Your payment details will be stored, and you'll be charged for each of these deliveries at your specific frequency.

If you want to cancel or change your subscription, you can do it at any time. Your order confirmation emails have links to your order. You can manage your subscription from there or from the "[Manage Subscription](https://naturesway.com/account)" section of your account.

 Upon cancellation, your account created or registered with us (referred to as your "Account") will not be deleted, and you can still access your Account.

See our [returns policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal#Satisfaction%20Guarantee) for more details on returns and refunds.

8. **Product Use**

Regulations for product use are established by country. Information contained on this site pertains only to United States, and is not intended to provide adequate information for product use. Before using any product, read and carefully observe the directions on the label.  Some products may not be available to ship to some states due to applicable state laws.

9. **Links to Third-Party Services**

The Services may contain links to other services ("Linked Services"). The Linked Services are not under the control of Schwabe North America, and Schwabe North America is not responsible for the content of the Linked Services, including, without limitation, links contained on Linked Services, or any changes or updates to Linked Services. Schwabe North America is providing Linked Services to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of such Linked Services is not an endorsement by Schwabe North America in favor of any company offering Internet services, products or services on the Linked Services.

10. **Copyright Rights**

All copyright rights in the text, images, photographs, graphics, user interface, and other content provided on the Site, and the selection, coordination, and arrangement of such content, are owned by Schwabe North America or its affiliates, subsidiaries or third-party licensors, to the full extent provided under the United States Copyright Act and all international copyright laws. Under applicable copyright laws, you are prohibited from copying, reproducing, modifying, distributing, displaying, performing or transmitting any of the contents of the Services for any purposes. Nothing stated or implied on the Site confers on you any license or right under any copyright of Schwabe North America or any third party.

The Service and the information contained in reference herein are for informational purposes only. Any reproduction, copying, or redistribution for commercial purposes of any materials or design elements of the Services is strictly prohibited, without the prior written consent of Schwabe North America. Requests for permission to reproduce any information contained on this Site should be addressed to Schwabe North America, Inc. Attn: Legal Department, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311, e-mail: privacyquestion@naturesway.com.

Notwithstanding the above, Schwabe North America authorizes you to make one (1) electronic or paper copy of the information posted on any page of the Services, provided that the copy is used solely for non-commercial, personal purposes, and further provided that any such copy remains protected by all copyright, trademarks, service marks, and other proprietary notices and legends contained on the Service. Systematic retrieval of data or other content from the Services to create, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory without written permission from Schwabe North America is prohibited.

11. **Trade and Service Mark Rights**

All rights in the product names, company names, trade names, logos, product packaging and designs of all Schwabe North America or third-party products or services, whether or not appearing in large print or with the trademark symbol, belong exclusively to Schwabe North America or their respective owners, and are protected from reproduction, imitation, dilution or confusing or misleading uses under national and international trademark and copyright laws. The use or misuse of these trademarks or any materials, except as permitted herein, is expressly prohibited and nothing stated or implied on this Service confers on you any license or right under any patent or trademark of Schwabe North America or any third party. 

12. **Submission of Questions and Release (“Ask the Expert”)**

By submitting a question in response to one of our requests or questions on @natureswaybrands  Instagram stories or via our Ask the Expert submission form on the Site (“Your Question”), you grant us, our agents, affiliates, and/or related entities a non-exclusive, royalty-free, irrevocable, worldwide, perpetual, and transferable license to use Your Question, your name, and your handle (“Your Content”) in any media, including, but not limited to, on its webpages, social, marketing, third party materials, promotional materials, advertising, and any other commercial purpose without any compensation to you.  We may use, reproduce, distribute, combine with other materials, alter and/or edit Your Content in any manner in its sole discretion, without any obligation or additional permission from you. 

Your Question is deemed to be non-confidential and non-proprietary.  We are under no obligation to use Your Question. You agree to cooperate with us and sign any supporting documentation we may reasonably require, confirming our ownership, including copyright ownership and your waiver of any applicable moral rights. 

Any personal identifiable information collected in providing Your Question will be collected by us or our agent and used by us as described in these Terms and in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20Policy). 

You represent and warrant to us that (i) you are 18 years old or older and a legal resident of the 50 United States; (ii) have the right to transmit Your Content; (iii) you are the copyright owner or have the copyright owner’s permission required to grant the rights to Your Content; (iv) you hold the rights necessary to grant the licenses described herein; (iv) Your Content will not violate, misappropriate or infringe any intellectual property rights, publicity rights or other proprietary rights of any third party. 

You hereby release us from any claims, damages, actions or liabilities arising from our use of Your Content as permitted herein. 

You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless us from and against all losses, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees arising from any breach of the foregoing representations and warranties.

13. **User Generated Content Terms of Service (“UGC Terms of Service”)**

The "Content" refers to the photo(s), video(s), story(ies), caption and comments you posted on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or Pinterest ("Social Media") described in the message we sent referring you to these UGC Terms of Service.  In addition, the Content may include your responses to questions we sent you in a message regarding your use of our products, any photos or videos you provide directly to us, as well as any product reviews you posted on Social Media or provided directly to us.

**By responding to our message with the requested hashtag or response, you agree that we may use your Content in accordance with these UGC Terms of Service.**

You represent and warrant that:

* You are at least eighteen (18) years of age or are legally considered an adult in the State or Country where you reside;
* You have full power and authority to agree to these UGC Terms of Service;
* The Content is your own original creation, you did not take the Content from another website, social media posting or elsewhere, and the Content does not contain anything that violates the rights of any person or entity;
* The Content does not contain any trademarks, logos, brand names, advertising, sponsorship, or promotional material owned by any person or entity, other than you or us;
* The Content does not contain anything illegal, defamatory, obscene or offensive;
* You have permission from any person(s) appearing in the Content to provide us with the rights to use the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service;
* Your upload or post of the Content does not violate any applicable laws or the terms or requirements of the Social Media platform(s) where you uploaded or posted the Content;
* Our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service will not violate the rights of any person or entity and will not violate any law;
* You confirm and agree that Our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service does not and shall not require any payment to any person or entity and does not require license, authorization, approval or consent by any other person or entity; and
* You have read and you agree to comply with all of the terms and conditions in these UGC Terms of Service.

You grant us an irrevocable and unlimited right and license to use the Content (and to allow others to use the Content) including allowing us to feature your name, social media handle, accompanying text, and any images, without the payment of any royalty. You agree that you shall never withdraw this permission and license to use the Content. We may use the Content for any business purpose on our websites and social media pages, and in our digital newsletters, and any other online, digital marketing material and in any new media or technology that becomes available later in time, throughout the world, for an unlimited time. You agree that we may use, copy, , modify, alter, edit, publish, create new derivative works from, make available and display the Content (or any part of the Content) and related content, and include the Content (or any part of the Content) into other works, for any business related purposes, including but not limited to promotional and marketing purposes. You also grant us the right, at our sole choice, to use your username, real name, image, likeness, caption, location or other identifying information in connection with any use of the Content. You agree that we have no obligation to use the Content or your name or other identifying information.

You confirm that you have the consent or permission of any other person or entity that is required for our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service, including but not limited to: (a) any person who appears or performs in the Content, and (b) any person or entity who owns any rights in the Content or anything that appears in the Content. You irrevocably and unconditionally grant to us all consents or permissions of any person or entity as required by any applicable laws, including but not limited to Copyright laws and related rights laws (and all other laws now or in future in force in any part of the world) which may be required for our use of the Content and the rights you are granting us under these UGC Terms of Service.

You irrevocably and unconditionally waive (and agree not to enforce) all rights in the Content, including without limitation any moral rights or equivalent rights which you may otherwise have under any laws now existing or which become law in the future in any part of the world.

If requested, you will sign any documentation in such manner and at such location as may be required to protect, perfect or enforce any of the rights you have given to us under these UGC Terms of Service. Whether we choose to use the Content or not is solely our choice. We have no obligation to use the Content and we may remove or stop using any Content at any time, for any reason. Use of the Content does not imply our endorsement of or any affiliation with you.

We will use any personal data we receive in connection with our use of the Content in accordance with these UGC Terms of Service and in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal#Privacy%20Policy).

If you believe that the Content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, you may provide us with written notification of your claim in accordance with the requirements of the U.S. Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 and the instructions provided in these Site Terms of Service.

You shall be liable for and shall indemnify us against any and all claims, actions, liabilities, losses, damages, expenses (including reasonable legal expenses) incurred by us which arise directly or indirectly from a breach by you of your obligations, representations or warranties under these UGC Terms of Service.

These UGC Terms of Service are personal to you and may not be assigned or transferred by you for any reason whatsoever without our prior written consent. We may assign our rights and obligations under these UGC Terms of Service to any other person, in whole or in part, without consent.

A failure by us to exercise and any delay, forbearance or indulgence by us in exercising any right, power or remedy under these UGC Terms of Service (in whole or in part) shall not operate as a waiver of that right, power or remedy or preclude its exercise at any subsequent time or on any subsequent occasion. A person not a party to these UGC Terms of Service has no right to enforce any of these terms.

These UGC Terms of Service contain all the terms agreed between us regarding the Content and supersede any prior agreement, understanding or arrangement between us, whether oral or in writing.

Any questions regarding these UGC Terms of Service may be directed to: Schwabe North America, Inc., Attn: General Counsel, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311.

14. **Customer Ratings, Reviews, and Submissions**

We welcome your reviews, comments, submissions, and any other content you submit through the Site.  By submitting any such content, you allow us to feature, such as your name, social media handle, accompanying text, and any images (collectively, “User Submissions”). 

By submitting any User Submissions, you agree that:

* You are the sole author and owner of the intellectual property rights in the User Submissions;
* All "moral rights" that you may have in such User Submissions have been voluntarily waived by you;
* All User Submissions that you post is accurate;
* You are at least 18 years old;
* Use of the User Submissions you supply does not violate these Site Terms of Service and will not cause injury to any person or entity.

You further agree that you may not submit any User Submissions:

* That is known by you to be false, inaccurate or misleading;
* That infringes any third party's copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy;
* That violates any law, statute, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to, those governing, consumer protection, unfair competition, anti-discrimination or false advertising);
* That is, or may reasonably be considered to be, defamatory, libelous, hateful, racially or religiously biased or offensive, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing to any individual, partnership or corporation;
* For which you were compensated or granted any consideration by any unapproved third party;
* That includes any information that references other websites, addresses, email addresses, contact information or phone numbers;
* That contains any computer viruses, worms or other potentially damaging computer programs or files.

You agree to indemnify and hold us (and our officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures, employees and third-party service providers, including, but not limited to, Bazaarvoice, Inc.), harmless from all claims, demands, and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind and nature, known and unknown including reasonable attorneys' fees, arising out of a breach of your representations and warranties set forth above, or your violation of any law or the rights of a third party.

For any User Submissions that you submit, you grant Schwabe North America a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, transferable right and license to use , copy, modify, delete in its entirety, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from and/or sell and/or distribute such User Submissions and/or incorporate such User Submissions into any form, medium or technology throughout the world without compensation to you.

All User Submissions that you submit may be used at our sole discretion. We reserve the right to change, condense, withhold publication, remove or delete any content on the Site that we deem, in our sole discretion, to violate the User Submissions’ guidelines above or any other provision of these Site Terms of Service.  We do not guarantee that you will have any recourse through Schwabe North America to edit or delete any User Submissions you have submitted. Ratings and written comments are generally posted within two to four business days. However, we reserve the right to remove or to refuse to post any submission to the extent authorized by law. You acknowledge that you, not Schwabe North America, are responsible for the contents of your User Submissions. None of the User Submissions that you submit shall be subject to any obligation of confidence on the part of Schwabe North America, its agents, subsidiaries, affiliates, partners or third party service providers and their respective directors, officers and employees.

Please note that Site visitors may post content that is inaccurate, misleading, or deceptive. Schwabe North America neither endorses nor is responsible for any opinion, advice, information, or statements made by third parties. The opinions expressed by third parties reflect solely the opinions of the individuals who submitted such opinions and may not reflect the opinions of Schwabe North America.

15. **Modification of These Site Terms of Service**

Schwabe North America reserves the right to amend these Terms of Service at any time. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current Terms of Service to which you are bound. Your use of the Services after the posting of modifications to these Terms of Service will constitute your acceptance of these Terms of Service, as modified. If at any time you do not wish to accept these Terms of Service, you are not thereafter authorized to use the Services.

16. **Updating Your Information**

If you need to update any of your online and/or off-line contact information, please send an email to Schwabe North America Customer Care at info@naturesway.com  or a letter to Schwabe North America, Attn: Customer Care, Schwabe North America, Inc., 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311.

17. **Disclaimer of Warranties**

THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS." SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER RELATING TO THE SERVICE, OR OTHER CONTENT OR WEBSITES THAT MAY BE ACCESSIBLE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY THROUGH THE SERVICE. SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA DISCLAIMS TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ANY AND ALL (i) WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, (ii) WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OR PROPRIETARY RIGHTS, (iii) WARRANTIES RELATING TO DELAYS, INTERRUPTIONS, ERRORS, OR OMISSIONS IN THE SERVICE, OR ANY PART THEREOF, (iv) WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE TRANSMISSION OR DELIVERY OF THE SERVICE, (v) WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CORRECTNESS OR COMPLETENESS OF DATA, AND (vi) WARRANTIES OTHERWISE RELATING TO PERFORMANCE, NONPERFORMANCE, OR OTHER ACTS OR OMISSIONS BY SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA OR ANY THIRD PARTY. FURTHER, THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR NEEDS OR REQUIREMENTS OR THE NEEDS OR REQUIREMENTS OF ANY OTHER PERSON.

SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, THAT THE INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE FROM ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, OR DELAY IN OPERATION. ANY INFORMATION ON THIS SITE IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE, AND WE DISCLAIM ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR THESE CHANGES.

18. **Limitation of Liability**

IN NO EVENT WILL SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA OR ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SERVICES, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE, MISUSE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICES OR ANY LINKED SERVICES, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE.

SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA RESERVES THE RIGHT TO ALTER THE CONTENT OF THIS SERVICE IN ANY WAY, AT ANY TIME, FOR ANY REASON, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTIFICATION, AND WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR POSSIBLE CONSEQUENCES OF SUCH CHANGES. THESE LIMITATIONS APPLY EVEN IF SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.  BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA'S LIABILITY IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

19. **Indemnification**

Upon a request by Schwabe North America, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Schwabe North America and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners and employees from all liabilities, claims and expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the Service, your violation of these Terms of Service or your violation of any rights of another.

20. **Digital Millennium Copyright Act / Notice of Copyright Infringement**

If you believe that your work has been copied and is accessible on this Site in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide Schwabe North America's Copyright Agent with the following information:

* Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed;
* Identification of the allegedly infringing material on the Service that is requested to be removed;
* Your name, address and daytime telephone number, and an e-mail address if available, so that Schwabe North America may contact you if necessary;
* A statement that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
* A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the signatory is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive copyright right that is allegedly infringed; and
* An electronic or physical signature of the copyright owner or someone authorized on the owner's behalf to assert infringement of copyright and to submit the statement.

Schwabe North America's Copyright Agent for Notice of claims of copyright infringement on the Service can be reached as follows: Legal Department Copyright Agent Schwabe North America, Inc. 825 Challenger Drive Green Bay, WI 54311 e-mail: privacyquestion@naturesway.com.

Any notice that fails to comply with the above requirements will not be considered sufficient notice. Schwabe North America will remove any content which infringes the copyright of any person under the laws of the United States upon receipt of such a statement (or, more specifically, any statement in conformance with 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(3)). United States law provides significant penalties for submitting such a statement falsely.

21. **Choice of Law and Forum**

These Site Terms of Service shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Wisconsin, excluding its conflict of law rules. You and Schwabe North America expressly agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the courts in Wisconsin in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the Services.

22. **No Waiver**

The failure of Schwabe North America to enforce any provisions of these of Terms of Service or respond to a breach by you or other parties shall not in any way waive its right to enforce subsequently any terms or conditions of these Terms of Service or to act with respect to similar breaches.

23. **Miscellaneous**

You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and Schwabe North America as a result of these Terms of Service or your use of the Services. Nothing contained in these Terms of Service is in derogation of Schwabe North America's right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of these Services or information provided to or gathered by Schwabe North America with respect to such use. A printed version of these Site Terms of Service and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to these Site Terms of Service to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.

24. **Severability and Integration**

Unless otherwise specified herein, these Terms of Service constitute the entire agreement between you and Schwabe North America.

#### Satisfaction Guarantee

#### Our Guarantee To You

We believe our obsession with quality makes for better supplements. It’s why we devote time and resources to rigorously test and approve our products. It’s also why we offer a 45-day satisfaction guarantee when you purchase your Nature’s Way product from naturesway.com or an authorized seller.

**45-Day Satisfaction Guarantee**

We want you to be confident in the Nature’s Way product you’ve selected for your wellness routine. If for any reason you are not satisfied with a Nature’s Way product you purchased for personal use from us or one of our authorized sellers, we want to make it right.

**Return Policy**

If you are not satisfied with your purchase for any reason, you may return it within 45 days of the date of your purchase for a full refund, excluding any shipping charges. Please keep your packing slip or confirmation email for proof of purchase. We monitor return activity for abuse and reserve the right to limit or refuse returns or exchanges.

We reserve the right to request the product be shipped back to us in its original packaging at the customer’s expense and we do not assume responsibility for lost or misdirected returns. Please note that clearance items, as well as short-dated and expired product are not eligible for an exchange or refund.

**How to Submit Your Claim**

To obtain a refund for product purchased directly on Naturesway.com, or if you are unable to obtain a refund from the authorized seller from which you purchased your product, please call one of our Customer Care Team at 1-800-962-8873. Please have information available regarding where and when you purchased your product. Upon approval of your request, you will then need to mail your Nature’s Way product, a proof of purchase (such as your receipt), and your Guarantee approval confirmation number to:

Nature’s Way Brands  
Attn: Customer Care  
825 Challenger Dr.  
Green Bay, WI 54311

Your Guarantee request must be submitted within 45 days of the date of your purchase, and you are responsible for costs incurred in mailing your product and proof of purchase. All refunds issued will be for the product purchase price, exclusive of taxes and fees. If you select a replacement product instead of a refund, you may select a product of equal or lesser value.

Our 45-day guarantee only applies to products sold on naturesway.com or by authorized sellers of Nature’s Way products. This is because we’re unable to control the quality of products sold by unauthorized sellers. We’re in constant pursuit of the highest quality supplements – a mission we take seriously. Give our team a call if you have questions about any Nature’s Way supplement.

**Guarantee Guidelines**

Nature’s Way reserves the right to verify information, require a valid proof of purchase, request return of product and to deny Guarantee requests in its sole discretion in cases of suspected fraud or if an individual has abused the Nature’s Way 45-Day Satisfaction Guarantee.

#### Accessibility

Nature’s Way is committed to making our website accessible to all. It’s another way we help people live healthy lives. Whether you’re using assistive technologies like screen readers, magnifiers, voice recognition software, or captions on videos, our goal is to make your experience on Naturesway.com a good one.

We look at this process as an ongoing effort and continue to work on enhancing the accessibility of our site. We’re taking steps and devoting resources to this important endeavor. Please [contact us](https://naturesway.com/pages/contact "contact us") if you have questions, feedback, or suggestions.

#### Promotions

Take up to 30% off sitewide for Black Friday Cyber Monday, no code necessary. 

Offer is to receive up to 30% off only on the merchandise displayed on \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/promotions](https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Femailview.naturesway.com%2Fe3t%2FCtc%2FGG%2B113%2Fd2ymY-04%2FVX18D78_t1yvW7wJgvl72LRnQW1sXT7r5p51VpMfRfk-3qgyTW7lCdLW6lZ3pxV8C7pr5L3rFyW7P_p995D5dTjW7qJ43t2mwZmZW1Pcysw3DHcsNW3rd6ns7kdw8VW83TnqK14Ygl7V9gSKf2Fdk-GW8FFRRB1t8sWPVDDXXq9czrTgW4Xg1TP429jQqW6XZ7qy1xQR6CW3kZdK_45GfnkW5zHj-G83yMFKW7-C_ff57M8kVW5kkLk322DmBPW2z_tDY3x4GyKW42M6xW782M_DVKCQ969dLtPlW8-wk-L5QnSBLW8Fr9HG1hzD9WW8B1qk93f2LyQMVV6D090DPDW4X0Xxz6LVp4YW48wMpk4QwrGwf8gz-Vq04&data=05%7C02%7Cmeredith.smith%40naturesway.com%7Cbd165a8632de496ab77f08dd12f3fec9%7C75175fd5f77746be9748efc2fa9d2135%7C0%7C0%7C638687561369839156%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&sdata=pZcWMaWrE9AN0pvMs3Ui%2FtQ0oMdyci%2B9TaS7zvxDL2c%3D&reserved=0 "https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3a%2f%2femailview.naturesway.com%2fe3t%2fctc%2fgg%2b113%2fd2ymy-04%2fvx18d78_t1yvw7wjgvl72lrnqw1sxt7r5p51vpmfrfk-3qgytw7lcdlw6lz3pxv8c7pr5l3rfyw7p_p995d5dtjw7qj43t2mwzmzw1pcysw3dhcsnw3rd6ns7kdw8vw83tnqk14ygl7v9gskf2fdk-gw8ffrrb1t8swpvddxxq9czrtgw4xg1tp429jqqw6xz7qy1xqr6cw3kzdk_45gfnkw5zhj-g83ymfkw7-c_ff57m8kvw5kklk322dmbpw2z_tdy3x4gykw42m6xw782m_dvkcq969dltplw8-wk-l5qnsblw8fr9hg1hzd9ww8b1qk93f2lyqmvv6d090dpdw4x0xxz6lvp4yw48wmpk4qwrgwf8gz-vq04&data=05%7c02%7cmeredith.smith%40naturesway.com%7cbd165a8632de496ab77f08dd12f3fec9%7c75175fd5f77746be9748efc2fa9d2135%7c0%7c0%7c638687561369839156%7cunknown%7ctwfpbgzsb3d8eyjfbxb0eu1hcgkionrydwusilyioiiwljaumdawmcisilaioijxaw4zmiisikfoijoitwfpbcisilduijoyfq%3d%3d%7c0%7c%7c%7c&sdata=pzcwmawre9an0pvms3ui%2ftq0omdyci%2b9tas7zvxdl2c%3d&reserved=0")\]. No code necessary, discounts automatically applied at checkout. Code good from 11/25 at 12:01am CDT to 12/3 at 11:59pm CDT. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Does not include Integrative Therapeutics, Overstock, Subscribe & Save, or Bundle & Save offers. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited. 

Up to 25% off Overstock items

Offer is to receive up to 25% off only on the merchandise displayed on   \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/overstock](https://naturesway.com/collections/overstock)\]. Discounts are applied to the price shown, and no code is necessary. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. All sales of overstock items are final and not eligible for returns or exchanges. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

40-60% off products in Last Chance

Offer is to receive up to 60% off only on the merchandise displayed on   \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance](https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance]. "https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance].")\]. Discounts are applied to the price shown, and no code is necessary. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. All sales of last chance items are final and not eligible for returns or exchanges. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited. 

25% off select products with code EXPLORENW

Offer valid from 10/1/2023 until 6/30/25 at 11:59pm CDT. Offer applies to all products listed at \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/explore-natures-way](https://naturesway.com/collections/explore-natures-way)\] using the code at checkout. Valid on merchandise only at naturesway.com. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.

20% off your first order with email sign-up

Enter promo code from your email at checkout to redeem. Offer limited to one-time use only online at naturesway.com and is non-transferable. Offer applies to merchandise on naturesway.com only and is not valid on applicable taxes or shipping and handling charges. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. No adjustments on previous purchases. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Cannot be combined with other offers or discounts. Nature’s Way is not responsible for lost or stolen coupon codes and reserves the right to alter, modify, or discontinue this offer at any time. Additional exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

15% off your first order with email sign-up

Enter promo code from your email at checkout to redeem. Offer limited to one-time use only online at naturesway.com and is non-transferable. Offer applies to merchandise on naturesway.com only and is not valid on applicable taxes or shipping and handling charges. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. No adjustments on previous purchases. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Cannot be combined with other offers or discounts. Nature’s Way is not responsible for lost or stolen coupon codes and reserves the right to alter, modify, or discontinue this offer at any time. Additional exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

#### Giveaway

NATURE’S WAY® 2024 HOLIDAY GIVEAWAY

OFFICIAL RULES

**NO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. YOU MUST HAVE INTERNET ACCESS IN ORDER TO PARTICIPATE.**

By participating in the Nature’s Way (“Nature’s Way”) 2024 Holiday Giveaway (“Giveaway”), you unconditionally accept and agree to comply with these Official Rules (“Official Rules”) and the decisions of Nature’s Way Brands, LLC (“Sponsor”) shall be final and binding in all respects.

1. **GIVEAWAY ENTRY PERIOD**. The Giveaway begins at 9:00:00 A.M. Central Time (CT) on December 1, 2024 and ends at 11:59 P.M. CT on December 15, 2024 (“Giveaway Period”).

1. **ELIGIBILITY**. Open to residents of the fifty (50) United States, including the District of Columbia, who are 18 years of age or older at time of entry. Employees of Sponsor, its parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, advertising and promotion agencies (“Promotion Entities”) and its immediate family members and/or those living in the same household of each are not eligible to participate. Void where prohibited.

1. **ENTRY METHOD**. During the Giveaway Period, to enter to win the Prize (as defined in Section 4), you must log into your Instagram account and (i) like the Giveaway post; (ii) follow @natureswaybrands; and (iii) tag one (1) friend in the comments using the hashtag #NaturesWayGiveaway (the “Entry”). Please note Instagram profile does not need to be public.

All Entries are subject to confirmation by Sponsor. Limit one (1) Entry into the Giveaway per person, per Instagram account. **No purchase or payment of any kind is necessary. Sponsor reserves the right to disqualify any entry for non-compliance with these Official Rules.**

No automated entry devices, bots, and/or other programs and/or software are permitted for entry. Sponsor is not responsible for lost, late illegible, incomplete, invalid, unintelligible, misdirected, technically corrupted or garbled entries, which will be disqualified, or for problems of any kind, whether mechanical, human or electronic. Only Entries that meet the Entry requirements are eligible. 

In the event of a dispute over the identity of an entrant in the Giveaway, participation will be deemed completed by the Authorized Account Holder of the Instagram account provided at the time of participation. “Authorized Account Holder” is defined as the natural person who is assigned to an Instagram account by Instagram. Only fully completed Entries are eligible. 

**This Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Instagram LLC.** 

**IMPORTANT: MESSAGE AND DATA RATES MAY APPLY TO USE OF MOBILE PHONE/DEVICE TO PARTICIPATE IN GIVEAWAY. INSTAGRAM IS FREE TO DOWNLOAD AND AVAILABLE FOR iPHONE FROM THE APPLE APPLICATION STORE AND FOR ANDROID FROM THE GOOGLE PLAY STORE.**

1. **PRIZES/APPROXIMATE RETAIL VALUES (ARV)/ODDS**: There is a total of one (1) prize (the “Prize”), consisting of: (i) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Organic Apple Cider Vinegar Gummies (60 count) (ARV: $17.49); (ii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Ashwagandha (60 Count) (ARV: $24.99); (iii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Sambucus Traditional Immune Syrup (ARV: $17.99); (iv) one (1) Capri Blue® Apple Cider Social Candle (ARV: $28.00); (v) one (1) set of Lululemon® Wunder Puff® Mittens (ARV: $78.00); (vi) one (1) Williams Sonoma® Snowman Mug (ARV: $59.95); (vii) one (1) Smeg® Mini Kettle (ARV: $150.00); (viii) one (1) Ugg® Home Kirkwood Throw (ARV: $88.00); and (ix) one (1) Amazon® Kindle Paperwhite® 6.8” e-Reader with Adjustable Warm Light (ARV: $132.99).

**The total ARV of the Prize is $597.41.**

Limit one (1) Prize per person, per physical mailing address, and per Instagram account. Decisions regarding the invalidity or validity of any Entry will be made at Sponsor’s sole discretion and all such decisions are binding and final. Any potential Prize winner who does not reply to a prize notification with the required information and within the specified time period will be disqualified and an alternate winner may be notified. All applicable federal, state, and local taxes on Prizes are the sole responsibility of Giveaway recipient. Winner will be issued an IRS 1099-MISC tax form for the prize retail value, if applicable.

Odds of winning will depend upon the timing of eligible Entries received during the Giveaway Period and the total number of eligible Entries received during the Giveaway Period.

**This Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands.**

One (1) winner will be selected at random on December 16, 2024. The Prize will be awarded within thirty (30) days of winner confirmation. Sponsor reserves the right to revoke Prize from any winner who it deems, in its sole discretion, may have violated any policy or law, and/or may bring the Sponsor into disrepute. In the event a Prize winner engages in behavior that, as determined by the Sponsor in its sole discretion, is inappropriate, obnoxious, threatening, illegal or that is intended to annoy, abuse, threaten or harass, victimize, degrade, or intimidate any other individual or group of individuals, including, but not limited to, on the basis of religion, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender, age or disability, or that in any way disparages or adversely affects the reputation, image, and/or goodwill of Sponsor or any of their services, products, trademarks, service marks, or logos, Sponsor reserves the right to terminate the Prize, or violates the rights of any other party, including but not limited to intellectual property rights or rights of privacy, publicity or other moral rights, in whole or in part, with no further obligation or compensation whatsoever to such Prize winner. 

1. **WINNER NOTIFICATION**: A potential winner will be notified via Direct Message (“DM”) and will be required to provide his/her/their full name, address, and phone number within three (3) days of receipt of DM. Noncompliance will result in disqualification.

1. **GENERAL**: If the Prize is returned as non-deliverable, the Prize will be forfeited and may be given to another entrant in accordance with these Official Rules. No cash equivalents, substitutions or transfer of Prize permitted except that Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a Prize of equal or greater value in the event that an offered product is unavailable. Subject to all federal, state and local laws/regulations. By accepting a Prize, winner releases and agrees to hold harmless Promotion Entities, including without limitation, their respective directors, employees, officers, and agents, including without limitation, from any and all liability, injury, loss or damage of any kind, including but not limited to personal injury or death, arising from or in connection with participation in the Giveaway, or the awarding, receipt, possession, use or misuse of any Prize and/or respect to participation in any Prize related activity. Neither Promotion Entities, including without limitation nor their employees will have any liability whatsoever for any injuries, losses or damages of any kind caused by any Prize or resulting from acceptance, possession, use and/or misuse of any Prize or participation in the promotion or any Prize-related activities.  Except where prohibited by law, acceptance of a Prize shall be construed as and signify the winner’s agreement and consent that Sponsor may use the winner’s name, voice, likeness and/or information, without limitation, for promotional purposes without further consideration, review, approval or payment, where allowed by law. Winners acknowledge that neither Sponsor nor its agents have made nor are in any manner responsible or liable for any warranty, representation or guarantee, express or implied, in fact or in law, relative to any Prize, including, but not limited to, its quality, mechanical condition or fitness for a particular purpose. Sponsor is not responsible for any typographical or other error in the printing of the offer or in administration of the Giveaway.

1. **LIMITATIONS AND RELEASES**: By participating in the Giveaway, entrants and winners agree to release, indemnify, and hold harmless Sponsor and their respective subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions, partners, representatives, agents, successors, assigns, employees, officers and directors, as well as Instagram LLC and their respective subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions, partners, representatives, agents, successors, assigns, employees, officers and directors (the "Released Parties"), from any and all liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever, including without limitation, property damage, personal injury (including emotional distress), and/or death, which may occur in connection with preparation for, or participation in, the Giveaway, or possession, acceptance and/or use or misuse of the Prize or participation in any Giveaway\-related or Prize-related activity and for any claims or causes of action based on publicity rights, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery. The Released Parties assume no responsibility for any injury or damage to entrants or to any other person's computer, regardless of how caused, relating to or resulting from entering or downloading materials or software in connection with this Giveaway. Entrants and winners acknowledge that Sponsor has neither made nor is in any manner responsible or liable for any warranty, representations or guarantees, express or implied, in fact or in law, relative to any prize or any component thereof, including, but not limited to, express warranties provided by the supplier of the Prize (or any component thereof) or their affiliates.

Promotion Entities are not responsible for lost, late, mutilated or illegible entries nor for electronic transmission errors resulting in omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operations or transmission, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to or alterations of entry materials, or for technical, network, telephone equipment, electronic, computer, hardware or software malfunctions or limitations of any kind, or inaccurate transmissions of or failure to receive entry information by Sponsor on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website or any combination thereof. Sponsor reserves the right to modify, extend, suspend, or terminate the Giveaway if it determines, in its sole discretion, that the Giveaway is technically impaired or corrupted or that fraud or technical problems, failures or malfunctions or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control have destroyed or severely undermined or to any degree impaired the integrity, administration, security, proper play and/or feasibility of the Giveaway as contemplated herein. In the event Sponsor is prevented from awarding Prizes or continuing with the Giveaway as contemplated herein by any event beyond its control, Sponsor shall have the right to modify, suspend, or terminate the Giveaway. The invalidity or unenforceability of any provision of these Official Rules shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision. In the event that any provision is determined to be invalid or otherwise unenforceable or illegal, these Official Rules shall otherwise remain in effect and shall be construed in accordance with their terms as if the invalid or illegal provision were not contained herein. Caution: Any attempt by any person to deliberately damage any website or undermine the legitimate operation of the Giveaway is a violation of law and should such an attempt be made, Sponsor reserves the right to seek damages from any such person to the fullest extent of the law.

1. **PRIVACY**: For information about how Sponsor uses your personal information, please see its privacy policy, located at [https://www.naturesway.com/Privacy-Policy](https://www.naturesway.com/Privacy-Policy).

1. **GOVERNING LAW/JURISDICTION**: ALL ISSUES AND QUESTIONS CONCERNING THE CONSTRUCTION, VALIDITY, INTERPRETATION AND ENFORCEABILITY OF THESE OFFICIAL RULES OR THE RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS OF ENTRANTS OR SPONSOR IN CONNECTION WITH THE GIVEAWAY SHALL BE GOVERNED BY AND CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE INTERNAL LAWS OF THE STATE OF WISCONSIN WITHOUT GIVING EFFECT TO ANY CHOICE OF LAW OR CONFLICT OF LAW RULES OR PROVISIONS THAT WOULD CAUSE THE APPLICATION OF ANY OTHER STATE’S LAWS. ENTRANTS AGREE (AND AGREE TO CONFIRM IN WRITING) THAT: (I) ANY AND ALL DISPUTES, CLAIMS AND CAUSES OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR CONNECTED WITH THIS GIVEAWAY SHALL BE RESOLVED INDIVIDUALLY, WITHOUT RESORT TO ANY FORM OF CLASS ACTION, AND EXCLUSIVELY BY THE APPROPRIATE COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION TO BE UNENFORCEABLE; (II) ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, JUDGMENTS AND AWARDS SHALL BE LIMITED TO ACTUAL OUT-OF-POCKET COSTS INCURRED, BUT IN NO EVENT ATTORNEYS’ FEES; AND (III) UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL ENTRANT BE PERMITTED TO OBTAIN AWARDS FOR AND ENTRANT HEREBY WAIVES ALL RIGHTS TO CLAIM PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL AND/OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES AND ANY OTHER DAMAGES, OTHER THAN FOR ACTUAL OUT-OF-POCKET EXPENSES, AND ANY AND ALL RIGHTS TO HAVE DAMAGES MULTIPLIED OR OTHERWISE INCREASED. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.  THE GIVEAWAY IS SUBJECT TO ALL APPLICABLE FEDERAL, STATE AND LOCAL/MUNICIPAL LAWS AND IS VOID WHERE PROHIBITED BY LAW. IF ANY PROVISION OF THESE OFFICIAL RULES IS FOUND BY ANY COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION TO BE UNENFORCEABLE, ALL OTHER PROVISIONS WILL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.

1. **WINNER CONFIRMATION REQUEST**: To obtain the name of the Giveaway winners, send a written request with a self-addressed, stamped envelope to: Attn: Marketing Department, NATURE’S WAY BRANDS, LLC, 100 N 6th St Suite 210C, Minneapolis, MN 55403.

1. **SPONSOR**: NATURE’S WAY BRANDS, LLC, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311

1. **SOCIAL MEDIA**: Instagram is a registered trademark of Instagram, LLC. This Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram. Any information provided for the purposes of entry in the Giveaway is provided to Sponsor, and not to Instagram. Any questions, comments or complaints regarding the Giveaway must be directed to the Sponsor and not to Instagram. Instagram and all of their affiliates, directors, officers, agents and employees are not liable for any claims arising out of or in connection with the organization of this Giveaway. However, by entering this Giveaway, each entrant agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of use and other policies or guidelines governing the use of the specific social platform and releases the Sponsor and the Released Parties from and against any damage that could arise from the use of such platforms.

**ABBREVIATED RULES**: \*NO PURCHASE NECESSARY. Subject to the Official Rules available in LINK IN BIO or at https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Giveaway. Open to legal residents of 50 United States and District of Columbia who are 18 years old or older at the time of entry. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED OR RESTRICTED BY LAW. Entry period begins at 9:00 a.m. CST on 12/01/2024 and ends at 11:59 p.m. CST on 12/15/2024. One (1) winner will be selected at random on 12/16/2024 and contacted directly via direct message (DM) on Instagram. LIMIT: 1 Entry per entrant. Winner will receive one (1) prize consisting of: (i) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Organic Apple Cider Vinegar Gummies (60 count) (ARV: $17.49); (ii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Ashwagandha (60 Count) (ARV: $24.99); (iii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Sambucus Traditional Immune Syrup (ARV: $17.99); (iv) one (1) Capri Blue® Apple Cider Social Candle (ARV: $28.00); (v) one (1) set of Lululemon® Wunder Puff® Mittens (ARV: $78.00); (vi) one (1) Williams Sonoma® Snowman Mug (ARV: $59.95); (vii) one (1) Smeg® Mini Kettle (ARV: $150.00); (viii) one (1) Ugg® Home Kirkwood Throw (ARV: $88.00); and (ix) one (1) Amazon® Kindle Paperwhite® 6.8” e-Reader with Adjustable Warm Light (ARV: $132.99). The total ARV of the Prize is $597.41. Limits, restrictions, instructions, and prize information are set forth in the Official Rules. Sponsor: Nature’s Way Brands, LLC. 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, Wisconsin 543111. Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands. All trademarks and brand names are the property of their respective owners. Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram.

**SUPER ABBREVIATED RULES**: \*NO PURCH. NEC. Subject to Official Rules available in LINK IN BIO or at [https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Giveaway](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/%23Giveaway). Open to legal residents of 50 U.S. & D.C. who are 18 y.o. or older at the time of entry. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED OR RESTRICTED BY LAW. Entry period begins at 9:00 a.m. CST on 12/01/24 & ends at 11:59 CST on 12/15/24. LIMIT: One (1) Entry per entrant. One (1) prize in total available as detailed in the Official Rules. One (1) winner will be selected at random and notified directly by direct message (DM) on Instagram. The total ARV of the prize is $597.41. Sponsor: Nature’s Way Brands, LLC. 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311. Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands. All trademarks and brand names are the property of their respective owners. Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram.

#### Do Not Sell or Share My Data

This website uses cookies and other tracking technologies to enhance user experience and to analyze performance and traffic on our website. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. If we have detected an opt-out preference signal, then it will be honored. Further information on our policy is available in our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal "Privacy Policy") 

Or if you have a personal request, please complete the, Exercise My Rights form below. This form allows you to make the following requests:

* Access to the Information that Nature's Way has related to you and your activities on our website. 
* Request Nature's Way to delete the information about you and your activities on our website.
* Request Nature's Way not to sell or share your data. Nature's Way works with partners that support a friendly informative journey on and off our website.
* Request Nature's Way to correct your personal information.

Thank you for choosing Nature's Way.  

#### Consumer Health Privacy Policy

**Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy**

This policy governs the websites (each a “Site”), apps (each an “App”), offline locations or services (collectively, the “Services”) owned and operated by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC, or its affiliates and subsidiaries (referred to herein as “Nature’s Way,” “we,” “us,” or “our” as applicable) that display, reference, or link to this Health Data Privacy Policy. This policy supplements the [Nature’s Way Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20of%20Policy) and applies to “consumer health data” subject to Washington State’s My Health My Data Act (MHMDA).

**CONSUMER HEALTH DATA WE COLLECT**

* Some of the products we sell and services that we provide to our customers may result in the collection of data that qualifies as “consumer health data,” as defined by the MHMDA. When we collect such data, it falls into the following categories: Products or services that may reveal information about your health-related conditions, symptoms, status, diagnoses, testing, or treatments.
* Products or services that may reveal information about your bodily functions, vital signs, reproductive or sexual health, weight and fitness-related goals/activities, and exercise habits/goals.
* Precise location information that could reasonably reveal your use of health services or supplies.
* Products or services that may reveal information that could identify your attempt to seek health related services.

* Other information that may be used to infer or derive data related to the above or other health information.

**SOURCES OF CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

As described further in the “Collection of Information” section of the [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20of%20Policy), we collect consumer health data directly from you, from your interactions with our Services, from third parties, including Affiliates, and from publicly available sources.

**WHY WE COLLECT AND USE CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

We may use the categories of consumer health data described above for the following purposes:

**Communicating with You.** We use consumer health data to respond to your questions and comments when you communicate with us through links or pages in the Services, such as the "Contact Us" feature.

**Processing Your Transactions.** If you purchase products from us on or through the Services, we use your consumer health data to process your purchase, confirm your order, and deliver the items to you.

**Administering the Services.** We use your consumer health data to administer the Services and carry out any other business activities.

**Abandoned Cart.** We use technologies to help keep track of the items you put into your cart, including when you have abandoned your cart, and use this information to determine when to send a cart reminder via SMS or other channels.

**Providing You with Personalized Recommendations.** If you choose to complete assessments in the Services, we will use your consumer health data to send you personalized product recommendations and other information that may be of interest to you.

**Performing Analyses.** We use your consumer health data to perform business analyses or for other purposes designed to improve the quality of our business and the Services we offer.

**Preventing and Detecting Fraud and Other Crimes.** We use your consumer health data to help prevent and detect fraud and other crimes that might be committed using or against the Services. We may use your consumer health data to investigate possible violations of and enforce our contracts.

**Managing and Operating Our IT Systems.** We use your consumer health data to help us in troubleshooting, testing, maintaining, and protecting our IT systems, including our Sites.

**Complying with Legal and Regulatory Obligations.** We use your consumer health data to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, which arise from time to time. We may also use your consumer health data to protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates. We do this to protect our business assets and to comply with our legal obligations.

**Promotions, Surveys, Sweepstakes, and Message Boards.** We use your consumer health data to enable you to voluntarily participate in features such as promotions, surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards in the Services.

**Creating Aggregate or Anonymized Information.** We use consumer health data you provide to us regarding the Services to provide product feedback to our customers in aggregated form. We may also use aggregate consumer health data to analyze general trends in the use of the Services.

**As Otherwise Permitted by Law or as We May Notify You.** We may also use consumer health data you provide to us for other purposes as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.

**WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

As defined by MHMDA, we share consumer health data with the categories of third parties listed below. We will obtain your consent before sharing your consumer health data.  

**Affiliates.** We may share your consumer health data with our Affiliates to send you promotions, information about sales and offers, and newsletters in which you have indicated interest and for legal and other business purposes.

**Business Partners.** We may share your consumer health data with companies with whom we partner to offer goods or services, including jointly provided products, or sweepstakes, contests, and similar and promotions.

**Competent Governmental and Public Authorities.** We may share your consumer health data with governmental authorities if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity or a violation of our Terms and Conditions (posted at the footer of our Site) or other contracts.

**Third Parties Pursuant to Legal Process.** We may share your consumer health data to the extent necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; in response to a request for cooperation from law enforcement or a government agency; or to otherwise comply with our other legal and regulatory obligations.

**Other Third Parties.** We may share your consumer health data when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, including to allow us to pursue available remedies and limit the damage we may sustain. To the extent we share your consumer health data with other third parties, we will do so in accordance with MHMDA.

**HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS**

MHMDA provides covered individuals with certain rights to access, delete, or withdraw consent relating to their consumer health data, subject to certain exceptions. 

If you would like to exercise the rights outlined above, please follow the prompts [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963) or by email at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com). If you send a request by email, please write “Consumer Health Data Request” in the subject line and state which rights you seek to exercise in the body of your message. We may take steps to verify your identity before responding to your request by asking you a series of questions about your previous interactions with us.

If your request to exercise a right under the MHMDA is denied, you may appeal that decision by emailing us at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com). If your appeal is unsuccessful, you can raise a concern or lodge a complaint with the Washington State Attorney General at [www.atg.wa.gov/file-complaint](http://www.atg.wa.gov/file-complaint) or the Nevada State Attorney General at [https://ag.nv.gov/Complaints/File\_Complaint/.](https://ag.nv.gov/Complaints/File_Complaint/)

**REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on our Services. Your continued use of our products and Services following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. If we change this policy in a material or substantive way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us by email at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com).

Effective: March 31, 2024                   Last updated: April 15, 2024

* Privacy Policy
* Terms of Service
* Satisfaction Guarantee
* Accessibility
* Promotions
* Giveaway
* Do Not Sell or Share My Data
* Consumer Health Privacy Policy

Nature’s Way - Website Privacy Policy  
  
Last Modified: November 11, 2024

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites, social media pages, mobile applications, or online services that are owned or controlled by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Nature’s Way,” “our,” “we,” or “us”) and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Sites,” and individually, a “Site”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Sites and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Nature’s Way (unless specifically stated). This Privacy Policy describes our information collection and use practices, as well as rights you may have with respect to the personal information we collect.  
  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website owned or operated by any third party even if such third party links to a Site or if Nature’s Way links to that third-party website. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any third party or business partner that Nature’s Way does not own or control. Your use of this website is also governed by our [Terms of Service](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Terms%20of%20Service). Please review this Policy and our Terms before using the Sites. By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, do not access or use the Sites.

**NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**  
  
California Notice at Collection  
  
We collect Personal Information as detailed here and in our Privacy Policy. The following serves as our notice at collection of Personal Information in accordance with California law. As defined by applicable law, we may “sell” or “share” certain Personal Information. If you would like to opt out of the sale or sharing of your Personal Information, you may do so [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963). You may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”). We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt out.  
  
We keep Personal Information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also keep Personal Information as otherwise required by law. What this means in practice will vary between different types of information, and when we consider our approach we take into account ongoing business or legal needs for the information, for example in relation to tax, health and safety, and potential or actual disputes or investigations.  
  
We collect your Personal Information as disclosed in the “Collection of Information Section” below.  
  
**1\. DEFINITIONS**  
  
For purposes of this Privacy Policy:  
  
“Aggregate or De-Identified Information” means information about groups or categories of data, which does not identify and cannot reasonably be used to identify an individual.  
  
“Cookies” means unique identifiers that a website places on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device when you visit the website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its Privacy Policy.  
  
“Flash Cookies” means local shared objects that are used to store personalized information based on visits to websites.  
  
“Personal Information” means information that identifies or is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household, such as the individual’s name, postal address, email address or telephone number.  
  
“Web Beacons” means small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its Privacy Policy.  
  
**2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
  
We collect information in different ways. We collect information listed in the “What Categories of Information we Collect About You” section below when you provide us that information voluntarily. For example, if you register an account with us, contact us for information, or participate in a promotion.  
  
We also collect information about you automatically. Where permitted by law we use tracking tools such as browser Cookies and Web Beacons to collect information from you. We collect information about users over time when you use the Sites. We collect information about you from third parties, such as social media platforms and advertising analytics providers. We may have third parties collect information as described in this Privacy Policy, for example in Section 6.  
  
We may collect information about you from third parties and commercially-available sources, including from social media providers, survey providers, data aggregators, data brokers, and public or commercially-available databases. We may collect information about your interactions with our ads on third-party sites. We may also collect information about you from our service providers, affiliates, and business partners.  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| What categories of Personal Information do we collect? | What are the purposes for which we collect and use your Personal Information? |
| * _Identifiers_: This includes your real name, postal address, Internet Protocol address, telephone number, email address, or other similar identifiers.<br>* _Characteristics of Protected Classifications:_ This includes your age, race, color, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), medical condition, physical or mental disability, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, marital status, veteran or military status, and genetic information (including familial genetic information).<br>* _Commercial Information:_ This includes records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.<br>* _Internet or other Electronic Network Activity Information:_ This includes browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.<br>* _Geolocation Data:_ This includes physical location or movements.<br>* _Audio Information:_ This includes data relating to call transcripts with Nature’s Way personnel.<br>* _Professional or employment-related information:_ This includes information related to your employment and employment history.<br>* _Inferences Drawn from Above:_ This includes a profile reflecting a person’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | * We use information to respond to your requests or questions.<br>* We use information to improve our Sites, products, programs and services.<br>* We might use your information to customize your experience with us.<br>* We use information to administer our Site and for internal operations. For example, we may aggregate or de-identify your information for analytics, research or other business purposes. We combine information. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online, to the extent permitted by law, for the transactional purpose, or by your consent. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.<br>* We use information for security purposes. Where legally permitted, we may use your information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.<br>* We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products or services or special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about our products, services and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll send you our promotional emails.<br>* We use information to communicate with you about your account, purchases or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or for feedback. We might also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Site Usage Terms of Service.<br>* We use information to comply with applicable law, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law. |

**3\. USE OF INFORMATION**  
  
We may use the information we collect from and about you for a variety of business and commercial purposes, including:  
  
**Fulfilling your Request.** We use information that we collect including Personal Information for a variety of purposes. We use information to respond to your requests or questions, or to complete a transaction. We use information to improve our Sites, products, programs and services. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.  
  
**To Provide our Sites**. We use information to administer our Site and for internal operations. For example, we may aggregate or de-identify your information for analytics, research or other business purposes. We combine information. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.  
  
**Security and Fraud Prevention**. We use information for security purposes. Where legally permitted, we may use your information to protect our Company, our customers, and our Sites.  
  
**Targeted Advertising.** We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products or services or special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about our products, services and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll send you our promotional emails.  
  
**Providing You with Personalized Recommendations.** If you choose to complete assessments in the Services, we will use information that you provide to send you personalized product recommendations and other information that we believe may be of interest to you. We also use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertising and content, and to allow you to participate in interactive features, when you choose to do so. For example, we remember your login ID/email address or screen name so that you can quickly login the next time you visit the Services or so that you can easily retrieve the items you previously placed in your shopping cart.  
  
**Third-Party Social Networks**. We use your Personal Information when you interact with third-party social networking features, such as “Like” functions, to serve you with advertisements and engage with you on third-party social networks. You can learn more about how these features work and the profile data that we obtain about you, and find out how to opt out by reviewing the privacy notices of the relevant third-party social networks.  
  
**Performing Analyses**. We use your Personal Information to perform business analyses or for other purposes designed to improve the quality of our business and the Services we offer.  
  
**Preventing and Detecting Fraud and Other Crimes**. We use your Personal Information to help prevent and detect fraud and other crimes that might be committed using or against the Services. We may use your Personal Information to investigate possible violations of and enforce our contracts. We may also use your Personal Information to protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates. We do this to protect our business assets and to comply with our legal obligations.  
  
**Managing and Operating Our IT Systems**. We use your Personal Information to help us in troubleshooting, testing, maintaining, and protecting our IT systems, including our Sites.  
  
**Complying with Legal and Regulatory Obligations**. We use your Personal Information to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, which arise from time to time. For instance, we may use your contact information to alert you if a product is recalled.  
  
**Communicating with You.** We use information to communicate with you about your account, purchases or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or for feedback. We might also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Site Usage Terms of Service.  
  
We use information to comply with applicable law, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law.  
  
**4\. DISCLOSURE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION.**  
  
**Affiliates.** We are affiliated with a number of other health and wellness brands (collectively, our “Affiliates”). We may share your Personal Information with our Affiliates to send you promotions, information about sales and offers, and newsletters in which you have indicated interest and for legal and other business purposes.  
  
**Business Partners.** We may share your Personal Information with companies with whom we partner to offer goods or services (e.g., joint products or promotions).  
  
**Service Providers**. We may use third party service providers to perform certain services on behalf of the Sites, such as web site hosting, accepting job applications, providing web site usage analytics, sending email or other communications, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, providing consumer affairs services, fulfilling and processing orders, or performing other administrative services. Some of these service providers may collect information on the Sites directly from you on our behalf; in such cases, these service providers are not permitted to use your Personal Information for their own use.  
  
**Analytics and Advertising Partners.** You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from one or more third parties. If you agree at that time to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to that third party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties. You also may request, sometimes through your use of an interactive feature or third party application, that we share information about you with a third party, and we will typically do so under those circumstances.  
  
**Sponsors or Administrators.** We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (collectively, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list.  
  
We may also disclose your Personal Information: i) as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; ii) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a valid government request; or iii) if Nature’s Way is involved in a merger, acquisition, assignment, divestiture, bankruptcy, consolidation, reorganization, liquidation, transfer or sale of all or a portion of its assets.  
  
**5\. COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**  
  
We collect information, and authorize our third party vendors to collect information, about users over time across our Sites and for other services. To do this, we and/or our third party vendors use several common tracking tools. These may include Cookies, Web Beacons, Flash Cookies, and similar technologies.  
  
In connection with an email delivery and marketing company to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email messages and at our Site to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, how our visitors use our Site and to enable us to provide more focused and subsequent email marketing communications to you.  
  
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Sites are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with Web Beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content, which is often referred to as remarketing.  
  
While we may use a variety of service providers to perform advertising services, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.aspopens in a new tab, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/opens in a new tab, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an “opt-out” by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. Please note that these companies may still collect information when you are online and opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while visiting the Sites and elsewhere online.  
  
**6\. SECURITY AND RETENTION**  
  
Nature’s Way has reasonable technical and organizational security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of Personal Information under our control. However, given the nature of technology, we cannot guarantee that our systems are 100% secure. We periodically update our technology in order to improve the protection of customer information.  
  
We retain Personal Information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also keep Personal Information as otherwise required or permitted by law.  
  
**7\. WE STORE INFORMATION BOTH IN AND OUTSIDE OF THE U.S.**  
  
Personal Information we collect from you may be transferred to, or stored at, a destination in the United States or another destination outside of United States. It may be processed by staff operating in these locations who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your Personal Information to the United States. U.S. laws may not afford the same level or protection as those in your country.  
  
**8\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**  
  
Nature’s Way may make changes to this statement from time to time. We will post changes to our Privacy Policy here, so be sure to check back periodically.  
  
**9\. UNSUBSCRIBING FROM MARKETING MESSAGES**  
  
You may unsubscribe from receiving offers and promotions for our products and services through the unsubscribe mechanisms provided in our promotional communications. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.  
  
**10\. OUR SITES AND CHILDREN**  
  
Our Sites are meant for adults, and are not directed at children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 18 has given us information, you can contact us at privacyquestion@naturesway.com, or write to us at Customer Care at 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."  
  
**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
  
**Explanation of Applicable Privacy Rights**  
  
If you are a California, Virginia, Colorado or Connecticut resident, you may take advantage of the following privacy rights:  

* **Right to Know**: You have the right to request that we provide you with what Personal Information we have collected about you, including the categories of Personal Information, the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information, or for Virginians, what Personal Information is used for targeted advertising, the categories of third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information, and the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you. You have the right to receive this information in a portable format.

* **Right to Delete:** You have the right to request that we delete Personal Information that we have collected from you, subject to certain exceptions. Note that there are some reasons we will not be able to fully address your request, such as if we need to complete a transaction for you, to detect and protect against fraudulent and illegal activity, to exercise our rights, for our internal purposes, or to comply with a legal obligation.

* **Right to Correct:** You have the right to request that we correct inaccurate Personal Information that we may maintain about you, subject to appropriate verification.

* **Right to Opt-Out of the Sale or Sharing of, or Targeted Advertising using, Personal Information:** You may have the right to opt-out of the "sale" or "sharing" of, or targeted advertising using, your Personal Information, as such terms are defined by applicable state privacy laws, to third parties, which may include our affiliated companies that do not share the same brand name. This means that, if you opt out, going forward, we will not sell or share your Personal Information with such third parties to use for their purposes, including, as applicable, for targeted advertising and cross-context behavioral advertising, unless you later direct us to do so.

* **Right to Limit:** You have the right to request that we limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive personal information.

* **Right to Appeal:** Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut residents also have the right to appeal a denial of their privacy rights.

**How to Submit a Request**  
  
For California, Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut residents, to take advantage of your right to know/access, delete, correct, or portability, or to submit an appeal of a denial of your privacy rights under Virginia, Colorado, or Connecticut law, please click [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963) or contact us by email at privacyquestion@naturesway.com, or by using the “Contact Us” section below. If by email, please indicate the type of request you are making in the subject line of your message. We may request certain information to verify your identity before we can respond to such requests. We will confirm receipt of your request within ten (10) business days and will respond to your request within forty-five (45) calendar days, after proper verification, unless we need additional time, in which case we will let you know.  
  
To take advantage of your right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of Personal Information or to opt-out of targeted advertising, please click on the [Do Not Sell or Share My Data](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Do%20Not%20Sell%20or%20Share%20My%20Data "Nature's Way Privacy Requests") link which also is on our site footer or contact us using the “Contact Us” section below. We will work to comply with your opt-out request within 15 business days.  
  
California, Connecticut, and Colorado residents may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal opt-out preference via a tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”). We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt out.  
  
We will not discriminate against you because you exercised your rights under this section of the Privacy Policy.  
  
**Agent Requests**  
  
You may authorize someone to make a privacy rights request on your behalf (an authorized agent). Authorized agents will need to demonstrate that you’ve authorized them to act on your behalf or must demonstrate they have power of attorney pursuant to applicable probate law. We retain the right to request confirmation directly from you confirming that the agent is authorized to make such a request, or to request additional information to confirm the agent’s identity. An authorized agent is prohibited from using a consumer’s Personal Information, or any information collected from or about the consumer, for any purpose other than to fulfill the consumer’s requests, for verification, or for fraud prevention. If you are making a request as an authorized agent, please contact us using the information in the “Contact Us” section below, and provide your full name, address, email address, the full name of the person on whose behalf you are making the request, their address, email, phone number, as well as the written permission of the person on whose behalf you are acting to do so.  
  
**Specific Data Protection Disclosures**  
  
Personal Information We Collect  
  
We have collected the categories of Personal Information disclosed in the “Notice to California Residents” section above, including within the last twelve (12) months.  
  
We Obtain the Categories of Personal Information Listed Above From the Following Categories of Sources:  

* Directly from you. For example, when you sign up for email on our Site.
* From other sources, such as marketing partners, social events, and social networking sites.
* Automatically through the use tracking technologies, as disclosed in the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section.

We collect Personal Information for the business and commercial purposes described in the “Use of Information” section above.  
  
Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for Business Purposes: We may disclose your Personal Information to a third party for a business purpose. When we disclose Personal Information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that Personal Information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.  
  
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the categories of Personal Information listed in the “Notice to California Residents” section above, for a business purpose.  
  
We disclose your Personal Information for the business purposes disclosed above in “Use of Information” to the following categories of third parties:  

* Our Affiliates.

* Service providers. We engage certain third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

Categories of Personal Information Sold or Shared  
  
Each category of Personal Information disclosed in “Personal Information We Collect” was sold or shared with analytics and advertising partners, business partners, advertising networks, advertising platforms, social media companies, and third parties, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy within the last 12 months, including for targeted advertising. We do not knowingly sell or share Personal Information about persons under the age of 16.

Schwabe North America, Inc. - Website Terms of Service Agreement

_Date Last Modified: November 11, 2024_

Schwabe North America and its subsidiaries and affiliates, including Nature’s Way Brands, LLC, ("Schwabe North America,” “we,” “our” or “us”) welcome you. The following Website Terms of Service Agreement ("Site Terms of Service") governs your use of this Internet website owned and operated by Schwabe North America (the "Site"). Please read these Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy carefully because they govern your use of the Site and our online store for our Products. The Site is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained in these Site Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy. For ease of reference, the Site and our online store are collectively called the “Services.”  

1. **Agreement to Site Terms of Service**

By accessing and using the Services, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions contained in these Site Terms of Service, you acknowledge: (i) that we will process your information; and (ii) to the use of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with our Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms set out in these Site Terms of Service, you must not use the Services.

2. **Your Obligations**

You are required to comply with all applicable laws in connection with your use of the Services, and such further limitations as may be set forth in any written or on-screen notice from Schwabe North America. As a condition of your use of the Services, you warrant that you will not use the Services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Site Terms of Service.

3. **Privacy Policy**

You agree and consent to the terms of the Schwabe North America Online Privacy Policy, a copy of which you should review by clicking [here](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20Policy).

4. **Availability of the Services**

We make no representations and provide no warranties that: (i) the Services will be made available at any time or from any specific geographical location; (ii) your access to the Services will be continuous or uninterrupted; or (iii) the Services will be accessible or optimized on all browser, computers, tablets, phones or viewing platforms.  We reserve the right to suspend access to all or part of the Services for any reason, including for business or operational reasons, such as improving the appearance or functionality of the Services, content updates, periodic maintenance, or to resolve any issues of which we become aware. The Services are provided for users in the United States. Although it may be possible to access the Services from other countries, we make no representation that the Services are compliant with any legal requirements in force in any jurisdiction other than United States, or that the content available on the Site will be appropriate for users in other countries.

5. **No Professional Advice**

Any information supplied through the Services or by any employee or agent of Schwabe North America, whether by telephone, e-mail, letter, facsimile or other form of communication, is for educational purposes or general guidance on the use of the Services, and does not constitute medical, legal, tax, accounting or other professional advice. Health-related information provided through the Services is not a substitute for medical advice and it is important that you not make medical decisions without first consulting your personal physician or health care practitioner. The information provided through the Services and on the Site does not replace the relationship that exists between you and your physician. **You should not use the information on this site for diagnosing or treating a health problem or disease**. Under no circumstances will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the Site.  The receipt of any questions or feedback you submit to Schwabe North America does not create a professional relationship and does not create any confidentiality privileges beyond those described in our Privacy Policy.  

6. **Online Product Purchases**

(a) Product Purchases. You may purchase products available on the Site. All products, specifications, descriptions, and prices are subject to change at any time without notice. Your purchase is subject to these Site Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to refuse any order you place with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order.  In the event that we make a change to or cancel an order, we may attempt to notify you by contacting the e-mail and/or billing address/phone number provided at the time the order was made.  

(b) Payment Information. You will be asked to enter your payment details during the checkout process. By placing an order, you confirm that the credit card you use is yours. All card payments are subject to authorization by your card issuer.

(c) Express Checkout. In addition, you can select an express check option: Shop Pay, Google Pay, or Apple Pay. When any of these payment options are selected, you are using that tool to manage payment, billing address, and shipping address.

(d) Shipping. Products you purchase through the Site will be shipped to you at the address you designate as the shipping address during the check-out process. We are not responsible for any packages that are refused or held for delivery. Refunds will not be issued for any orders that are refused by intended recipient or that cannot be delivered to due to an address error.  Currently, our Products are only available for purchase by residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia, and will only be shipped within the 50 United States and the District of Columbia. Free ground shipping on all orders of $35 or more. Some products may not be available to ship to some states due to applicable state laws.

(e) Return Policy. If you are not satisfied with your purchase for any reason, you may return it within 45 days of the date of your purchase for a full refund, excluding any shipping charges.  Please keep your packing slip or confirmation email for proof of purchase. We monitor return activity for abuse and reserve the right to limit or refuse returns or exchanges.

We reserve the right to request the product be shipped back to us in its original packaging at the customer’s expense and we do not assume responsibility for lost or misdirected returns. Please note that clearance items, as well as short-dated and expired product are not eligible for an exchange or refund.

7. **Subscribe & Save**

When you purchase a subscription you will regularly receive repeat deliveries. These are based on the subscription duration and frequency that you select. Your recurring subscription(s) will remain active until either you or Nature’s Way decides to cancel. You or Nature’s Way can terminate any recurring subscription at any time, and there will be no cancellation fee or ongoing charges after cancellation, except if a shipment in a recurring subscription has already been processed before cancellation. In such a case, the recurring subscription shipment will be canceled after that specific shipment, and you will be responsible for the payment of the last shipment.

Your payment details will be stored, and you'll be charged for each of these deliveries at your specific frequency.

If you want to cancel or change your subscription, you can do it at any time. Your order confirmation emails have links to your order. You can manage your subscription from there or from the "[Manage Subscription](https://naturesway.com/account)" section of your account.

 Upon cancellation, your account created or registered with us (referred to as your "Account") will not be deleted, and you can still access your Account.

See our [returns policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal#Satisfaction%20Guarantee) for more details on returns and refunds.

8. **Product Use**

Regulations for product use are established by country. Information contained on this site pertains only to United States, and is not intended to provide adequate information for product use. Before using any product, read and carefully observe the directions on the label.  Some products may not be available to ship to some states due to applicable state laws.

9. **Links to Third-Party Services**

The Services may contain links to other services ("Linked Services"). The Linked Services are not under the control of Schwabe North America, and Schwabe North America is not responsible for the content of the Linked Services, including, without limitation, links contained on Linked Services, or any changes or updates to Linked Services. Schwabe North America is providing Linked Services to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of such Linked Services is not an endorsement by Schwabe North America in favor of any company offering Internet services, products or services on the Linked Services.

10. **Copyright Rights**

All copyright rights in the text, images, photographs, graphics, user interface, and other content provided on the Site, and the selection, coordination, and arrangement of such content, are owned by Schwabe North America or its affiliates, subsidiaries or third-party licensors, to the full extent provided under the United States Copyright Act and all international copyright laws. Under applicable copyright laws, you are prohibited from copying, reproducing, modifying, distributing, displaying, performing or transmitting any of the contents of the Services for any purposes. Nothing stated or implied on the Site confers on you any license or right under any copyright of Schwabe North America or any third party.

The Service and the information contained in reference herein are for informational purposes only. Any reproduction, copying, or redistribution for commercial purposes of any materials or design elements of the Services is strictly prohibited, without the prior written consent of Schwabe North America. Requests for permission to reproduce any information contained on this Site should be addressed to Schwabe North America, Inc. Attn: Legal Department, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311, e-mail: privacyquestion@naturesway.com.

Notwithstanding the above, Schwabe North America authorizes you to make one (1) electronic or paper copy of the information posted on any page of the Services, provided that the copy is used solely for non-commercial, personal purposes, and further provided that any such copy remains protected by all copyright, trademarks, service marks, and other proprietary notices and legends contained on the Service. Systematic retrieval of data or other content from the Services to create, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory without written permission from Schwabe North America is prohibited.

11. **Trade and Service Mark Rights**

All rights in the product names, company names, trade names, logos, product packaging and designs of all Schwabe North America or third-party products or services, whether or not appearing in large print or with the trademark symbol, belong exclusively to Schwabe North America or their respective owners, and are protected from reproduction, imitation, dilution or confusing or misleading uses under national and international trademark and copyright laws. The use or misuse of these trademarks or any materials, except as permitted herein, is expressly prohibited and nothing stated or implied on this Service confers on you any license or right under any patent or trademark of Schwabe North America or any third party. 

12. **Submission of Questions and Release (“Ask the Expert”)**

By submitting a question in response to one of our requests or questions on @natureswaybrands  Instagram stories or via our Ask the Expert submission form on the Site (“Your Question”), you grant us, our agents, affiliates, and/or related entities a non-exclusive, royalty-free, irrevocable, worldwide, perpetual, and transferable license to use Your Question, your name, and your handle (“Your Content”) in any media, including, but not limited to, on its webpages, social, marketing, third party materials, promotional materials, advertising, and any other commercial purpose without any compensation to you.  We may use, reproduce, distribute, combine with other materials, alter and/or edit Your Content in any manner in its sole discretion, without any obligation or additional permission from you. 

Your Question is deemed to be non-confidential and non-proprietary.  We are under no obligation to use Your Question. You agree to cooperate with us and sign any supporting documentation we may reasonably require, confirming our ownership, including copyright ownership and your waiver of any applicable moral rights. 

Any personal identifiable information collected in providing Your Question will be collected by us or our agent and used by us as described in these Terms and in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20Policy). 

You represent and warrant to us that (i) you are 18 years old or older and a legal resident of the 50 United States; (ii) have the right to transmit Your Content; (iii) you are the copyright owner or have the copyright owner’s permission required to grant the rights to Your Content; (iv) you hold the rights necessary to grant the licenses described herein; (iv) Your Content will not violate, misappropriate or infringe any intellectual property rights, publicity rights or other proprietary rights of any third party. 

You hereby release us from any claims, damages, actions or liabilities arising from our use of Your Content as permitted herein. 

You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless us from and against all losses, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees arising from any breach of the foregoing representations and warranties.

13. **User Generated Content Terms of Service (“UGC Terms of Service”)**

The "Content" refers to the photo(s), video(s), story(ies), caption and comments you posted on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or Pinterest ("Social Media") described in the message we sent referring you to these UGC Terms of Service.  In addition, the Content may include your responses to questions we sent you in a message regarding your use of our products, any photos or videos you provide directly to us, as well as any product reviews you posted on Social Media or provided directly to us.

**By responding to our message with the requested hashtag or response, you agree that we may use your Content in accordance with these UGC Terms of Service.**

You represent and warrant that:

* You are at least eighteen (18) years of age or are legally considered an adult in the State or Country where you reside;
* You have full power and authority to agree to these UGC Terms of Service;
* The Content is your own original creation, you did not take the Content from another website, social media posting or elsewhere, and the Content does not contain anything that violates the rights of any person or entity;
* The Content does not contain any trademarks, logos, brand names, advertising, sponsorship, or promotional material owned by any person or entity, other than you or us;
* The Content does not contain anything illegal, defamatory, obscene or offensive;
* You have permission from any person(s) appearing in the Content to provide us with the rights to use the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service;
* Your upload or post of the Content does not violate any applicable laws or the terms or requirements of the Social Media platform(s) where you uploaded or posted the Content;
* Our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service will not violate the rights of any person or entity and will not violate any law;
* You confirm and agree that Our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service does not and shall not require any payment to any person or entity and does not require license, authorization, approval or consent by any other person or entity; and
* You have read and you agree to comply with all of the terms and conditions in these UGC Terms of Service.

You grant us an irrevocable and unlimited right and license to use the Content (and to allow others to use the Content) including allowing us to feature your name, social media handle, accompanying text, and any images, without the payment of any royalty. You agree that you shall never withdraw this permission and license to use the Content. We may use the Content for any business purpose on our websites and social media pages, and in our digital newsletters, and any other online, digital marketing material and in any new media or technology that becomes available later in time, throughout the world, for an unlimited time. You agree that we may use, copy, , modify, alter, edit, publish, create new derivative works from, make available and display the Content (or any part of the Content) and related content, and include the Content (or any part of the Content) into other works, for any business related purposes, including but not limited to promotional and marketing purposes. You also grant us the right, at our sole choice, to use your username, real name, image, likeness, caption, location or other identifying information in connection with any use of the Content. You agree that we have no obligation to use the Content or your name or other identifying information.

You confirm that you have the consent or permission of any other person or entity that is required for our use of the Content as described in these UGC Terms of Service, including but not limited to: (a) any person who appears or performs in the Content, and (b) any person or entity who owns any rights in the Content or anything that appears in the Content. You irrevocably and unconditionally grant to us all consents or permissions of any person or entity as required by any applicable laws, including but not limited to Copyright laws and related rights laws (and all other laws now or in future in force in any part of the world) which may be required for our use of the Content and the rights you are granting us under these UGC Terms of Service.

You irrevocably and unconditionally waive (and agree not to enforce) all rights in the Content, including without limitation any moral rights or equivalent rights which you may otherwise have under any laws now existing or which become law in the future in any part of the world.

If requested, you will sign any documentation in such manner and at such location as may be required to protect, perfect or enforce any of the rights you have given to us under these UGC Terms of Service. Whether we choose to use the Content or not is solely our choice. We have no obligation to use the Content and we may remove or stop using any Content at any time, for any reason. Use of the Content does not imply our endorsement of or any affiliation with you.

We will use any personal data we receive in connection with our use of the Content in accordance with these UGC Terms of Service and in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal#Privacy%20Policy).

If you believe that the Content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, you may provide us with written notification of your claim in accordance with the requirements of the U.S. Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 and the instructions provided in these Site Terms of Service.

You shall be liable for and shall indemnify us against any and all claims, actions, liabilities, losses, damages, expenses (including reasonable legal expenses) incurred by us which arise directly or indirectly from a breach by you of your obligations, representations or warranties under these UGC Terms of Service.

These UGC Terms of Service are personal to you and may not be assigned or transferred by you for any reason whatsoever without our prior written consent. We may assign our rights and obligations under these UGC Terms of Service to any other person, in whole or in part, without consent.

A failure by us to exercise and any delay, forbearance or indulgence by us in exercising any right, power or remedy under these UGC Terms of Service (in whole or in part) shall not operate as a waiver of that right, power or remedy or preclude its exercise at any subsequent time or on any subsequent occasion. A person not a party to these UGC Terms of Service has no right to enforce any of these terms.

These UGC Terms of Service contain all the terms agreed between us regarding the Content and supersede any prior agreement, understanding or arrangement between us, whether oral or in writing.

Any questions regarding these UGC Terms of Service may be directed to: Schwabe North America, Inc., Attn: General Counsel, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311.

14. **Customer Ratings, Reviews, and Submissions**

We welcome your reviews, comments, submissions, and any other content you submit through the Site.  By submitting any such content, you allow us to feature, such as your name, social media handle, accompanying text, and any images (collectively, “User Submissions”). 

By submitting any User Submissions, you agree that:

* You are the sole author and owner of the intellectual property rights in the User Submissions;
* All "moral rights" that you may have in such User Submissions have been voluntarily waived by you;
* All User Submissions that you post is accurate;
* You are at least 18 years old;
* Use of the User Submissions you supply does not violate these Site Terms of Service and will not cause injury to any person or entity.

You further agree that you may not submit any User Submissions:

* That is known by you to be false, inaccurate or misleading;
* That infringes any third party's copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy;
* That violates any law, statute, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to, those governing, consumer protection, unfair competition, anti-discrimination or false advertising);
* That is, or may reasonably be considered to be, defamatory, libelous, hateful, racially or religiously biased or offensive, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing to any individual, partnership or corporation;
* For which you were compensated or granted any consideration by any unapproved third party;
* That includes any information that references other websites, addresses, email addresses, contact information or phone numbers;
* That contains any computer viruses, worms or other potentially damaging computer programs or files.

You agree to indemnify and hold us (and our officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures, employees and third-party service providers, including, but not limited to, Bazaarvoice, Inc.), harmless from all claims, demands, and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind and nature, known and unknown including reasonable attorneys' fees, arising out of a breach of your representations and warranties set forth above, or your violation of any law or the rights of a third party.

For any User Submissions that you submit, you grant Schwabe North America a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, transferable right and license to use , copy, modify, delete in its entirety, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from and/or sell and/or distribute such User Submissions and/or incorporate such User Submissions into any form, medium or technology throughout the world without compensation to you.

All User Submissions that you submit may be used at our sole discretion. We reserve the right to change, condense, withhold publication, remove or delete any content on the Site that we deem, in our sole discretion, to violate the User Submissions’ guidelines above or any other provision of these Site Terms of Service.  We do not guarantee that you will have any recourse through Schwabe North America to edit or delete any User Submissions you have submitted. Ratings and written comments are generally posted within two to four business days. However, we reserve the right to remove or to refuse to post any submission to the extent authorized by law. You acknowledge that you, not Schwabe North America, are responsible for the contents of your User Submissions. None of the User Submissions that you submit shall be subject to any obligation of confidence on the part of Schwabe North America, its agents, subsidiaries, affiliates, partners or third party service providers and their respective directors, officers and employees.

Please note that Site visitors may post content that is inaccurate, misleading, or deceptive. Schwabe North America neither endorses nor is responsible for any opinion, advice, information, or statements made by third parties. The opinions expressed by third parties reflect solely the opinions of the individuals who submitted such opinions and may not reflect the opinions of Schwabe North America.

15. **Modification of These Site Terms of Service**

Schwabe North America reserves the right to amend these Terms of Service at any time. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current Terms of Service to which you are bound. Your use of the Services after the posting of modifications to these Terms of Service will constitute your acceptance of these Terms of Service, as modified. If at any time you do not wish to accept these Terms of Service, you are not thereafter authorized to use the Services.

16. **Updating Your Information**

If you need to update any of your online and/or off-line contact information, please send an email to Schwabe North America Customer Care at info@naturesway.com  or a letter to Schwabe North America, Attn: Customer Care, Schwabe North America, Inc., 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311.

17. **Disclaimer of Warranties**

THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS." SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER RELATING TO THE SERVICE, OR OTHER CONTENT OR WEBSITES THAT MAY BE ACCESSIBLE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY THROUGH THE SERVICE. SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA DISCLAIMS TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ANY AND ALL (i) WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, (ii) WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OR PROPRIETARY RIGHTS, (iii) WARRANTIES RELATING TO DELAYS, INTERRUPTIONS, ERRORS, OR OMISSIONS IN THE SERVICE, OR ANY PART THEREOF, (iv) WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE TRANSMISSION OR DELIVERY OF THE SERVICE, (v) WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CORRECTNESS OR COMPLETENESS OF DATA, AND (vi) WARRANTIES OTHERWISE RELATING TO PERFORMANCE, NONPERFORMANCE, OR OTHER ACTS OR OMISSIONS BY SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA OR ANY THIRD PARTY. FURTHER, THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR NEEDS OR REQUIREMENTS OR THE NEEDS OR REQUIREMENTS OF ANY OTHER PERSON.

SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, THAT THE INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE FROM ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, OR DELAY IN OPERATION. ANY INFORMATION ON THIS SITE IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE, AND WE DISCLAIM ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR THESE CHANGES.

18. **Limitation of Liability**

IN NO EVENT WILL SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA OR ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SERVICES, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE, MISUSE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICES OR ANY LINKED SERVICES, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE.

SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA RESERVES THE RIGHT TO ALTER THE CONTENT OF THIS SERVICE IN ANY WAY, AT ANY TIME, FOR ANY REASON, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTIFICATION, AND WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR POSSIBLE CONSEQUENCES OF SUCH CHANGES. THESE LIMITATIONS APPLY EVEN IF SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.  BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SCHWABE NORTH AMERICA'S LIABILITY IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

19. **Indemnification**

Upon a request by Schwabe North America, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Schwabe North America and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners and employees from all liabilities, claims and expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the Service, your violation of these Terms of Service or your violation of any rights of another.

20. **Digital Millennium Copyright Act / Notice of Copyright Infringement**

If you believe that your work has been copied and is accessible on this Site in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide Schwabe North America's Copyright Agent with the following information:

* Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed;
* Identification of the allegedly infringing material on the Service that is requested to be removed;
* Your name, address and daytime telephone number, and an e-mail address if available, so that Schwabe North America may contact you if necessary;
* A statement that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
* A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the signatory is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive copyright right that is allegedly infringed; and
* An electronic or physical signature of the copyright owner or someone authorized on the owner's behalf to assert infringement of copyright and to submit the statement.

Schwabe North America's Copyright Agent for Notice of claims of copyright infringement on the Service can be reached as follows: Legal Department Copyright Agent Schwabe North America, Inc. 825 Challenger Drive Green Bay, WI 54311 e-mail: privacyquestion@naturesway.com.

Any notice that fails to comply with the above requirements will not be considered sufficient notice. Schwabe North America will remove any content which infringes the copyright of any person under the laws of the United States upon receipt of such a statement (or, more specifically, any statement in conformance with 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(3)). United States law provides significant penalties for submitting such a statement falsely.

21. **Choice of Law and Forum**

These Site Terms of Service shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Wisconsin, excluding its conflict of law rules. You and Schwabe North America expressly agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the courts in Wisconsin in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the Services.

22. **No Waiver**

The failure of Schwabe North America to enforce any provisions of these of Terms of Service or respond to a breach by you or other parties shall not in any way waive its right to enforce subsequently any terms or conditions of these Terms of Service or to act with respect to similar breaches.

23. **Miscellaneous**

You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and Schwabe North America as a result of these Terms of Service or your use of the Services. Nothing contained in these Terms of Service is in derogation of Schwabe North America's right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of these Services or information provided to or gathered by Schwabe North America with respect to such use. A printed version of these Site Terms of Service and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to these Site Terms of Service to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.

24. **Severability and Integration**

Unless otherwise specified herein, these Terms of Service constitute the entire agreement between you and Schwabe North America.

#### Our Guarantee To You

We believe our obsession with quality makes for better supplements. It’s why we devote time and resources to rigorously test and approve our products. It’s also why we offer a 45-day satisfaction guarantee when you purchase your Nature’s Way product from naturesway.com or an authorized seller.

**45-Day Satisfaction Guarantee**

We want you to be confident in the Nature’s Way product you’ve selected for your wellness routine. If for any reason you are not satisfied with a Nature’s Way product you purchased for personal use from us or one of our authorized sellers, we want to make it right.

**Return Policy**

If you are not satisfied with your purchase for any reason, you may return it within 45 days of the date of your purchase for a full refund, excluding any shipping charges. Please keep your packing slip or confirmation email for proof of purchase. We monitor return activity for abuse and reserve the right to limit or refuse returns or exchanges.

We reserve the right to request the product be shipped back to us in its original packaging at the customer’s expense and we do not assume responsibility for lost or misdirected returns. Please note that clearance items, as well as short-dated and expired product are not eligible for an exchange or refund.

**How to Submit Your Claim**

To obtain a refund for product purchased directly on Naturesway.com, or if you are unable to obtain a refund from the authorized seller from which you purchased your product, please call one of our Customer Care Team at 1-800-962-8873. Please have information available regarding where and when you purchased your product. Upon approval of your request, you will then need to mail your Nature’s Way product, a proof of purchase (such as your receipt), and your Guarantee approval confirmation number to:

Nature’s Way Brands  
Attn: Customer Care  
825 Challenger Dr.  
Green Bay, WI 54311

Your Guarantee request must be submitted within 45 days of the date of your purchase, and you are responsible for costs incurred in mailing your product and proof of purchase. All refunds issued will be for the product purchase price, exclusive of taxes and fees. If you select a replacement product instead of a refund, you may select a product of equal or lesser value.

Our 45-day guarantee only applies to products sold on naturesway.com or by authorized sellers of Nature’s Way products. This is because we’re unable to control the quality of products sold by unauthorized sellers. We’re in constant pursuit of the highest quality supplements – a mission we take seriously. Give our team a call if you have questions about any Nature’s Way supplement.

**Guarantee Guidelines**

Nature’s Way reserves the right to verify information, require a valid proof of purchase, request return of product and to deny Guarantee requests in its sole discretion in cases of suspected fraud or if an individual has abused the Nature’s Way 45-Day Satisfaction Guarantee.

Nature’s Way is committed to making our website accessible to all. It’s another way we help people live healthy lives. Whether you’re using assistive technologies like screen readers, magnifiers, voice recognition software, or captions on videos, our goal is to make your experience on Naturesway.com a good one.

We look at this process as an ongoing effort and continue to work on enhancing the accessibility of our site. We’re taking steps and devoting resources to this important endeavor. Please [contact us](https://naturesway.com/pages/contact "contact us") if you have questions, feedback, or suggestions.

Take up to 30% off sitewide for Black Friday Cyber Monday, no code necessary. 

Offer is to receive up to 30% off only on the merchandise displayed on \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/promotions](https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Femailview.naturesway.com%2Fe3t%2FCtc%2FGG%2B113%2Fd2ymY-04%2FVX18D78_t1yvW7wJgvl72LRnQW1sXT7r5p51VpMfRfk-3qgyTW7lCdLW6lZ3pxV8C7pr5L3rFyW7P_p995D5dTjW7qJ43t2mwZmZW1Pcysw3DHcsNW3rd6ns7kdw8VW83TnqK14Ygl7V9gSKf2Fdk-GW8FFRRB1t8sWPVDDXXq9czrTgW4Xg1TP429jQqW6XZ7qy1xQR6CW3kZdK_45GfnkW5zHj-G83yMFKW7-C_ff57M8kVW5kkLk322DmBPW2z_tDY3x4GyKW42M6xW782M_DVKCQ969dLtPlW8-wk-L5QnSBLW8Fr9HG1hzD9WW8B1qk93f2LyQMVV6D090DPDW4X0Xxz6LVp4YW48wMpk4QwrGwf8gz-Vq04&data=05%7C02%7Cmeredith.smith%40naturesway.com%7Cbd165a8632de496ab77f08dd12f3fec9%7C75175fd5f77746be9748efc2fa9d2135%7C0%7C0%7C638687561369839156%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&sdata=pZcWMaWrE9AN0pvMs3Ui%2FtQ0oMdyci%2B9TaS7zvxDL2c%3D&reserved=0 "https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3a%2f%2femailview.naturesway.com%2fe3t%2fctc%2fgg%2b113%2fd2ymy-04%2fvx18d78_t1yvw7wjgvl72lrnqw1sxt7r5p51vpmfrfk-3qgytw7lcdlw6lz3pxv8c7pr5l3rfyw7p_p995d5dtjw7qj43t2mwzmzw1pcysw3dhcsnw3rd6ns7kdw8vw83tnqk14ygl7v9gskf2fdk-gw8ffrrb1t8swpvddxxq9czrtgw4xg1tp429jqqw6xz7qy1xqr6cw3kzdk_45gfnkw5zhj-g83ymfkw7-c_ff57m8kvw5kklk322dmbpw2z_tdy3x4gykw42m6xw782m_dvkcq969dltplw8-wk-l5qnsblw8fr9hg1hzd9ww8b1qk93f2lyqmvv6d090dpdw4x0xxz6lvp4yw48wmpk4qwrgwf8gz-vq04&data=05%7c02%7cmeredith.smith%40naturesway.com%7cbd165a8632de496ab77f08dd12f3fec9%7c75175fd5f77746be9748efc2fa9d2135%7c0%7c0%7c638687561369839156%7cunknown%7ctwfpbgzsb3d8eyjfbxb0eu1hcgkionrydwusilyioiiwljaumdawmcisilaioijxaw4zmiisikfoijoitwfpbcisilduijoyfq%3d%3d%7c0%7c%7c%7c&sdata=pzcwmawre9an0pvms3ui%2ftq0omdyci%2b9tas7zvxdl2c%3d&reserved=0")\]. No code necessary, discounts automatically applied at checkout. Code good from 11/25 at 12:01am CDT to 12/3 at 11:59pm CDT. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Does not include Integrative Therapeutics, Overstock, Subscribe & Save, or Bundle & Save offers. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited. 

Up to 25% off Overstock items

Offer is to receive up to 25% off only on the merchandise displayed on   \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/overstock](https://naturesway.com/collections/overstock)\]. Discounts are applied to the price shown, and no code is necessary. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. All sales of overstock items are final and not eligible for returns or exchanges. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

40-60% off products in Last Chance

Offer is to receive up to 60% off only on the merchandise displayed on   \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance](https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance]. "https://naturesway.com/collections/last-chance].")\]. Discounts are applied to the price shown, and no code is necessary. While Supplies Last. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. All sales of last chance items are final and not eligible for returns or exchanges. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited. 

25% off select products with code EXPLORENW

Offer valid from 10/1/2023 until 6/30/25 at 11:59pm CDT. Offer applies to all products listed at \[[https://naturesway.com/collections/explore-natures-way](https://naturesway.com/collections/explore-natures-way)\] using the code at checkout. Valid on merchandise only at naturesway.com. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. Not valid on applicable taxes or shipping & handling charges. No adjustments on previous purchases. Cannot be combined with other offers. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Offer is subject to change. Exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.

20% off your first order with email sign-up

Enter promo code from your email at checkout to redeem. Offer limited to one-time use only online at naturesway.com and is non-transferable. Offer applies to merchandise on naturesway.com only and is not valid on applicable taxes or shipping and handling charges. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. No adjustments on previous purchases. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Cannot be combined with other offers or discounts. Nature’s Way is not responsible for lost or stolen coupon codes and reserves the right to alter, modify, or discontinue this offer at any time. Additional exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

15% off your first order with email sign-up

Enter promo code from your email at checkout to redeem. Offer limited to one-time use only online at naturesway.com and is non-transferable. Offer applies to merchandise on naturesway.com only and is not valid on applicable taxes or shipping and handling charges. Excludes all Integrative Therapeutics products. No adjustments on previous purchases. Not valid for cash or cash equivalent. Cannot be combined with other offers or discounts. Nature’s Way is not responsible for lost or stolen coupon codes and reserves the right to alter, modify, or discontinue this offer at any time. Additional exclusions may apply. Void where prohibited.  

NATURE’S WAY® 2024 HOLIDAY GIVEAWAY

OFFICIAL RULES

**NO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. YOU MUST HAVE INTERNET ACCESS IN ORDER TO PARTICIPATE.**

By participating in the Nature’s Way (“Nature’s Way”) 2024 Holiday Giveaway (“Giveaway”), you unconditionally accept and agree to comply with these Official Rules (“Official Rules”) and the decisions of Nature’s Way Brands, LLC (“Sponsor”) shall be final and binding in all respects.

1. **GIVEAWAY ENTRY PERIOD**. The Giveaway begins at 9:00:00 A.M. Central Time (CT) on December 1, 2024 and ends at 11:59 P.M. CT on December 15, 2024 (“Giveaway Period”).

1. **ELIGIBILITY**. Open to residents of the fifty (50) United States, including the District of Columbia, who are 18 years of age or older at time of entry. Employees of Sponsor, its parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, advertising and promotion agencies (“Promotion Entities”) and its immediate family members and/or those living in the same household of each are not eligible to participate. Void where prohibited.

1. **ENTRY METHOD**. During the Giveaway Period, to enter to win the Prize (as defined in Section 4), you must log into your Instagram account and (i) like the Giveaway post; (ii) follow @natureswaybrands; and (iii) tag one (1) friend in the comments using the hashtag #NaturesWayGiveaway (the “Entry”). Please note Instagram profile does not need to be public.

All Entries are subject to confirmation by Sponsor. Limit one (1) Entry into the Giveaway per person, per Instagram account. **No purchase or payment of any kind is necessary. Sponsor reserves the right to disqualify any entry for non-compliance with these Official Rules.**

No automated entry devices, bots, and/or other programs and/or software are permitted for entry. Sponsor is not responsible for lost, late illegible, incomplete, invalid, unintelligible, misdirected, technically corrupted or garbled entries, which will be disqualified, or for problems of any kind, whether mechanical, human or electronic. Only Entries that meet the Entry requirements are eligible. 

In the event of a dispute over the identity of an entrant in the Giveaway, participation will be deemed completed by the Authorized Account Holder of the Instagram account provided at the time of participation. “Authorized Account Holder” is defined as the natural person who is assigned to an Instagram account by Instagram. Only fully completed Entries are eligible. 

**This Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Instagram LLC.** 

**IMPORTANT: MESSAGE AND DATA RATES MAY APPLY TO USE OF MOBILE PHONE/DEVICE TO PARTICIPATE IN GIVEAWAY. INSTAGRAM IS FREE TO DOWNLOAD AND AVAILABLE FOR iPHONE FROM THE APPLE APPLICATION STORE AND FOR ANDROID FROM THE GOOGLE PLAY STORE.**

1. **PRIZES/APPROXIMATE RETAIL VALUES (ARV)/ODDS**: There is a total of one (1) prize (the “Prize”), consisting of: (i) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Organic Apple Cider Vinegar Gummies (60 count) (ARV: $17.49); (ii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Ashwagandha (60 Count) (ARV: $24.99); (iii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Sambucus Traditional Immune Syrup (ARV: $17.99); (iv) one (1) Capri Blue® Apple Cider Social Candle (ARV: $28.00); (v) one (1) set of Lululemon® Wunder Puff® Mittens (ARV: $78.00); (vi) one (1) Williams Sonoma® Snowman Mug (ARV: $59.95); (vii) one (1) Smeg® Mini Kettle (ARV: $150.00); (viii) one (1) Ugg® Home Kirkwood Throw (ARV: $88.00); and (ix) one (1) Amazon® Kindle Paperwhite® 6.8” e-Reader with Adjustable Warm Light (ARV: $132.99).

**The total ARV of the Prize is $597.41.**

Limit one (1) Prize per person, per physical mailing address, and per Instagram account. Decisions regarding the invalidity or validity of any Entry will be made at Sponsor’s sole discretion and all such decisions are binding and final. Any potential Prize winner who does not reply to a prize notification with the required information and within the specified time period will be disqualified and an alternate winner may be notified. All applicable federal, state, and local taxes on Prizes are the sole responsibility of Giveaway recipient. Winner will be issued an IRS 1099-MISC tax form for the prize retail value, if applicable.

Odds of winning will depend upon the timing of eligible Entries received during the Giveaway Period and the total number of eligible Entries received during the Giveaway Period.

**This Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands.**

One (1) winner will be selected at random on December 16, 2024. The Prize will be awarded within thirty (30) days of winner confirmation. Sponsor reserves the right to revoke Prize from any winner who it deems, in its sole discretion, may have violated any policy or law, and/or may bring the Sponsor into disrepute. In the event a Prize winner engages in behavior that, as determined by the Sponsor in its sole discretion, is inappropriate, obnoxious, threatening, illegal or that is intended to annoy, abuse, threaten or harass, victimize, degrade, or intimidate any other individual or group of individuals, including, but not limited to, on the basis of religion, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender, age or disability, or that in any way disparages or adversely affects the reputation, image, and/or goodwill of Sponsor or any of their services, products, trademarks, service marks, or logos, Sponsor reserves the right to terminate the Prize, or violates the rights of any other party, including but not limited to intellectual property rights or rights of privacy, publicity or other moral rights, in whole or in part, with no further obligation or compensation whatsoever to such Prize winner. 

1. **WINNER NOTIFICATION**: A potential winner will be notified via Direct Message (“DM”) and will be required to provide his/her/their full name, address, and phone number within three (3) days of receipt of DM. Noncompliance will result in disqualification.

1. **GENERAL**: If the Prize is returned as non-deliverable, the Prize will be forfeited and may be given to another entrant in accordance with these Official Rules. No cash equivalents, substitutions or transfer of Prize permitted except that Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a Prize of equal or greater value in the event that an offered product is unavailable. Subject to all federal, state and local laws/regulations. By accepting a Prize, winner releases and agrees to hold harmless Promotion Entities, including without limitation, their respective directors, employees, officers, and agents, including without limitation, from any and all liability, injury, loss or damage of any kind, including but not limited to personal injury or death, arising from or in connection with participation in the Giveaway, or the awarding, receipt, possession, use or misuse of any Prize and/or respect to participation in any Prize related activity. Neither Promotion Entities, including without limitation nor their employees will have any liability whatsoever for any injuries, losses or damages of any kind caused by any Prize or resulting from acceptance, possession, use and/or misuse of any Prize or participation in the promotion or any Prize-related activities.  Except where prohibited by law, acceptance of a Prize shall be construed as and signify the winner’s agreement and consent that Sponsor may use the winner’s name, voice, likeness and/or information, without limitation, for promotional purposes without further consideration, review, approval or payment, where allowed by law. Winners acknowledge that neither Sponsor nor its agents have made nor are in any manner responsible or liable for any warranty, representation or guarantee, express or implied, in fact or in law, relative to any Prize, including, but not limited to, its quality, mechanical condition or fitness for a particular purpose. Sponsor is not responsible for any typographical or other error in the printing of the offer or in administration of the Giveaway.

1. **LIMITATIONS AND RELEASES**: By participating in the Giveaway, entrants and winners agree to release, indemnify, and hold harmless Sponsor and their respective subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions, partners, representatives, agents, successors, assigns, employees, officers and directors, as well as Instagram LLC and their respective subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions, partners, representatives, agents, successors, assigns, employees, officers and directors (the "Released Parties"), from any and all liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever, including without limitation, property damage, personal injury (including emotional distress), and/or death, which may occur in connection with preparation for, or participation in, the Giveaway, or possession, acceptance and/or use or misuse of the Prize or participation in any Giveaway\-related or Prize-related activity and for any claims or causes of action based on publicity rights, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery. The Released Parties assume no responsibility for any injury or damage to entrants or to any other person's computer, regardless of how caused, relating to or resulting from entering or downloading materials or software in connection with this Giveaway. Entrants and winners acknowledge that Sponsor has neither made nor is in any manner responsible or liable for any warranty, representations or guarantees, express or implied, in fact or in law, relative to any prize or any component thereof, including, but not limited to, express warranties provided by the supplier of the Prize (or any component thereof) or their affiliates.

Promotion Entities are not responsible for lost, late, mutilated or illegible entries nor for electronic transmission errors resulting in omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operations or transmission, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to or alterations of entry materials, or for technical, network, telephone equipment, electronic, computer, hardware or software malfunctions or limitations of any kind, or inaccurate transmissions of or failure to receive entry information by Sponsor on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website or any combination thereof. Sponsor reserves the right to modify, extend, suspend, or terminate the Giveaway if it determines, in its sole discretion, that the Giveaway is technically impaired or corrupted or that fraud or technical problems, failures or malfunctions or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control have destroyed or severely undermined or to any degree impaired the integrity, administration, security, proper play and/or feasibility of the Giveaway as contemplated herein. In the event Sponsor is prevented from awarding Prizes or continuing with the Giveaway as contemplated herein by any event beyond its control, Sponsor shall have the right to modify, suspend, or terminate the Giveaway. The invalidity or unenforceability of any provision of these Official Rules shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision. In the event that any provision is determined to be invalid or otherwise unenforceable or illegal, these Official Rules shall otherwise remain in effect and shall be construed in accordance with their terms as if the invalid or illegal provision were not contained herein. Caution: Any attempt by any person to deliberately damage any website or undermine the legitimate operation of the Giveaway is a violation of law and should such an attempt be made, Sponsor reserves the right to seek damages from any such person to the fullest extent of the law.

1. **PRIVACY**: For information about how Sponsor uses your personal information, please see its privacy policy, located at [https://www.naturesway.com/Privacy-Policy](https://www.naturesway.com/Privacy-Policy).

1. **GOVERNING LAW/JURISDICTION**: ALL ISSUES AND QUESTIONS CONCERNING THE CONSTRUCTION, VALIDITY, INTERPRETATION AND ENFORCEABILITY OF THESE OFFICIAL RULES OR THE RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS OF ENTRANTS OR SPONSOR IN CONNECTION WITH THE GIVEAWAY SHALL BE GOVERNED BY AND CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE INTERNAL LAWS OF THE STATE OF WISCONSIN WITHOUT GIVING EFFECT TO ANY CHOICE OF LAW OR CONFLICT OF LAW RULES OR PROVISIONS THAT WOULD CAUSE THE APPLICATION OF ANY OTHER STATE’S LAWS. ENTRANTS AGREE (AND AGREE TO CONFIRM IN WRITING) THAT: (I) ANY AND ALL DISPUTES, CLAIMS AND CAUSES OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR CONNECTED WITH THIS GIVEAWAY SHALL BE RESOLVED INDIVIDUALLY, WITHOUT RESORT TO ANY FORM OF CLASS ACTION, AND EXCLUSIVELY BY THE APPROPRIATE COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION TO BE UNENFORCEABLE; (II) ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, JUDGMENTS AND AWARDS SHALL BE LIMITED TO ACTUAL OUT-OF-POCKET COSTS INCURRED, BUT IN NO EVENT ATTORNEYS’ FEES; AND (III) UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL ENTRANT BE PERMITTED TO OBTAIN AWARDS FOR AND ENTRANT HEREBY WAIVES ALL RIGHTS TO CLAIM PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL AND/OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES AND ANY OTHER DAMAGES, OTHER THAN FOR ACTUAL OUT-OF-POCKET EXPENSES, AND ANY AND ALL RIGHTS TO HAVE DAMAGES MULTIPLIED OR OTHERWISE INCREASED. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.  THE GIVEAWAY IS SUBJECT TO ALL APPLICABLE FEDERAL, STATE AND LOCAL/MUNICIPAL LAWS AND IS VOID WHERE PROHIBITED BY LAW. IF ANY PROVISION OF THESE OFFICIAL RULES IS FOUND BY ANY COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION TO BE UNENFORCEABLE, ALL OTHER PROVISIONS WILL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.

1. **WINNER CONFIRMATION REQUEST**: To obtain the name of the Giveaway winners, send a written request with a self-addressed, stamped envelope to: Attn: Marketing Department, NATURE’S WAY BRANDS, LLC, 100 N 6th St Suite 210C, Minneapolis, MN 55403.

1. **SPONSOR**: NATURE’S WAY BRANDS, LLC, 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311

1. **SOCIAL MEDIA**: Instagram is a registered trademark of Instagram, LLC. This Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram. Any information provided for the purposes of entry in the Giveaway is provided to Sponsor, and not to Instagram. Any questions, comments or complaints regarding the Giveaway must be directed to the Sponsor and not to Instagram. Instagram and all of their affiliates, directors, officers, agents and employees are not liable for any claims arising out of or in connection with the organization of this Giveaway. However, by entering this Giveaway, each entrant agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of use and other policies or guidelines governing the use of the specific social platform and releases the Sponsor and the Released Parties from and against any damage that could arise from the use of such platforms.

**ABBREVIATED RULES**: \*NO PURCHASE NECESSARY. Subject to the Official Rules available in LINK IN BIO or at https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Giveaway. Open to legal residents of 50 United States and District of Columbia who are 18 years old or older at the time of entry. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED OR RESTRICTED BY LAW. Entry period begins at 9:00 a.m. CST on 12/01/2024 and ends at 11:59 p.m. CST on 12/15/2024. One (1) winner will be selected at random on 12/16/2024 and contacted directly via direct message (DM) on Instagram. LIMIT: 1 Entry per entrant. Winner will receive one (1) prize consisting of: (i) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Organic Apple Cider Vinegar Gummies (60 count) (ARV: $17.49); (ii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Ashwagandha (60 Count) (ARV: $24.99); (iii) one (1) bottle of Nature’s Way Sambucus Traditional Immune Syrup (ARV: $17.99); (iv) one (1) Capri Blue® Apple Cider Social Candle (ARV: $28.00); (v) one (1) set of Lululemon® Wunder Puff® Mittens (ARV: $78.00); (vi) one (1) Williams Sonoma® Snowman Mug (ARV: $59.95); (vii) one (1) Smeg® Mini Kettle (ARV: $150.00); (viii) one (1) Ugg® Home Kirkwood Throw (ARV: $88.00); and (ix) one (1) Amazon® Kindle Paperwhite® 6.8” e-Reader with Adjustable Warm Light (ARV: $132.99). The total ARV of the Prize is $597.41. Limits, restrictions, instructions, and prize information are set forth in the Official Rules. Sponsor: Nature’s Way Brands, LLC. 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, Wisconsin 543111. Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands. All trademarks and brand names are the property of their respective owners. Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram.

**SUPER ABBREVIATED RULES**: \*NO PURCH. NEC. Subject to Official Rules available in LINK IN BIO or at [https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/#Giveaway](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal/%23Giveaway). Open to legal residents of 50 U.S. & D.C. who are 18 y.o. or older at the time of entry. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED OR RESTRICTED BY LAW. Entry period begins at 9:00 a.m. CST on 12/01/24 & ends at 11:59 CST on 12/15/24. LIMIT: One (1) Entry per entrant. One (1) prize in total available as detailed in the Official Rules. One (1) winner will be selected at random and notified directly by direct message (DM) on Instagram. The total ARV of the prize is $597.41. Sponsor: Nature’s Way Brands, LLC. 825 Challenger Drive, Green Bay, WI 54311. Giveaway is sponsored by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC only, and is not affiliated with the Capri Blue®, Lululemon®, Williams Sonoma®, Smeg®, Ugg®, or the Amazon® brands. All trademarks and brand names are the property of their respective owners. Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Instagram.

This website uses cookies and other tracking technologies to enhance user experience and to analyze performance and traffic on our website. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. If we have detected an opt-out preference signal, then it will be honored. Further information on our policy is available in our [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/pages/legal "Privacy Policy") 

Or if you have a personal request, please complete the, Exercise My Rights form below. This form allows you to make the following requests:

* Access to the Information that Nature's Way has related to you and your activities on our website. 
* Request Nature's Way to delete the information about you and your activities on our website.
* Request Nature's Way not to sell or share your data. Nature's Way works with partners that support a friendly informative journey on and off our website.
* Request Nature's Way to correct your personal information.

Thank you for choosing Nature's Way.  

**Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy**

This policy governs the websites (each a “Site”), apps (each an “App”), offline locations or services (collectively, the “Services”) owned and operated by Nature’s Way Brands, LLC, or its affiliates and subsidiaries (referred to herein as “Nature’s Way,” “we,” “us,” or “our” as applicable) that display, reference, or link to this Health Data Privacy Policy. This policy supplements the [Nature’s Way Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20of%20Policy) and applies to “consumer health data” subject to Washington State’s My Health My Data Act (MHMDA).

**CONSUMER HEALTH DATA WE COLLECT**

* Some of the products we sell and services that we provide to our customers may result in the collection of data that qualifies as “consumer health data,” as defined by the MHMDA. When we collect such data, it falls into the following categories: Products or services that may reveal information about your health-related conditions, symptoms, status, diagnoses, testing, or treatments.
* Products or services that may reveal information about your bodily functions, vital signs, reproductive or sexual health, weight and fitness-related goals/activities, and exercise habits/goals.
* Precise location information that could reasonably reveal your use of health services or supplies.
* Products or services that may reveal information that could identify your attempt to seek health related services.

* Other information that may be used to infer or derive data related to the above or other health information.

**SOURCES OF CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

As described further in the “Collection of Information” section of the [Privacy Policy](https://naturesway.com/legal/#Privacy%20of%20Policy), we collect consumer health data directly from you, from your interactions with our Services, from third parties, including Affiliates, and from publicly available sources.

**WHY WE COLLECT AND USE CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

We may use the categories of consumer health data described above for the following purposes:

**Communicating with You.** We use consumer health data to respond to your questions and comments when you communicate with us through links or pages in the Services, such as the "Contact Us" feature.

**Processing Your Transactions.** If you purchase products from us on or through the Services, we use your consumer health data to process your purchase, confirm your order, and deliver the items to you.

**Administering the Services.** We use your consumer health data to administer the Services and carry out any other business activities.

**Abandoned Cart.** We use technologies to help keep track of the items you put into your cart, including when you have abandoned your cart, and use this information to determine when to send a cart reminder via SMS or other channels.

**Providing You with Personalized Recommendations.** If you choose to complete assessments in the Services, we will use your consumer health data to send you personalized product recommendations and other information that may be of interest to you.

**Performing Analyses.** We use your consumer health data to perform business analyses or for other purposes designed to improve the quality of our business and the Services we offer.

**Preventing and Detecting Fraud and Other Crimes.** We use your consumer health data to help prevent and detect fraud and other crimes that might be committed using or against the Services. We may use your consumer health data to investigate possible violations of and enforce our contracts.

**Managing and Operating Our IT Systems.** We use your consumer health data to help us in troubleshooting, testing, maintaining, and protecting our IT systems, including our Sites.

**Complying with Legal and Regulatory Obligations.** We use your consumer health data to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, which arise from time to time. We may also use your consumer health data to protect our or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates. We do this to protect our business assets and to comply with our legal obligations.

**Promotions, Surveys, Sweepstakes, and Message Boards.** We use your consumer health data to enable you to voluntarily participate in features such as promotions, surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards in the Services.

**Creating Aggregate or Anonymized Information.** We use consumer health data you provide to us regarding the Services to provide product feedback to our customers in aggregated form. We may also use aggregate consumer health data to analyze general trends in the use of the Services.

**As Otherwise Permitted by Law or as We May Notify You.** We may also use consumer health data you provide to us for other purposes as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.

**WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE CONSUMER HEALTH DATA**

As defined by MHMDA, we share consumer health data with the categories of third parties listed below. We will obtain your consent before sharing your consumer health data.  

**Affiliates.** We may share your consumer health data with our Affiliates to send you promotions, information about sales and offers, and newsletters in which you have indicated interest and for legal and other business purposes.

**Business Partners.** We may share your consumer health data with companies with whom we partner to offer goods or services, including jointly provided products, or sweepstakes, contests, and similar and promotions.

**Competent Governmental and Public Authorities.** We may share your consumer health data with governmental authorities if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity or a violation of our Terms and Conditions (posted at the footer of our Site) or other contracts.

**Third Parties Pursuant to Legal Process.** We may share your consumer health data to the extent necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; in response to a request for cooperation from law enforcement or a government agency; or to otherwise comply with our other legal and regulatory obligations.

**Other Third Parties.** We may share your consumer health data when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, including to allow us to pursue available remedies and limit the damage we may sustain. To the extent we share your consumer health data with other third parties, we will do so in accordance with MHMDA.

**HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS**

MHMDA provides covered individuals with certain rights to access, delete, or withdraw consent relating to their consumer health data, subject to certain exceptions. 

If you would like to exercise the rights outlined above, please follow the prompts [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/70b2067b-aab5-447b-ba95-fe5870617a82/7e04e93a-7c7d-40db-926a-89bc663c2963) or by email at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com). If you send a request by email, please write “Consumer Health Data Request” in the subject line and state which rights you seek to exercise in the body of your message. We may take steps to verify your identity before responding to your request by asking you a series of questions about your previous interactions with us.

If your request to exercise a right under the MHMDA is denied, you may appeal that decision by emailing us at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com). If your appeal is unsuccessful, you can raise a concern or lodge a complaint with the Washington State Attorney General at [www.atg.wa.gov/file-complaint](http://www.atg.wa.gov/file-complaint) or the Nevada State Attorney General at [https://ag.nv.gov/Complaints/File\_Complaint/.](https://ag.nv.gov/Complaints/File_Complaint/)

**REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on our Services. Your continued use of our products and Services following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. If we change this policy in a material or substantive way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us by email at [privacyquestion@naturesway.com](mailto:privacyquestion@naturesway.com).

Effective: March 31, 2024                   Last updated: April 15, 2024

#### Sign up for our newsletter to receive updates & discounts

Company

Products

Resources

More Info

#### Company

#### Products

#### Resources

#### More Info

#### Transparency Notice

\* This statement has not been evaluated by the Food & Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.

\*\* There are no valid studies using current scientific methods confirming this product’s efficacy. These indications are based solely on traditional homeopathic principles.

†† These indications are based solely on traditional homeopathic use. They have not been evaluated by the Food & Drug Administration.

© 2024. Nature's Way Brands, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.

Some text goes here Open the Real Chat

#### Hello there, looks like you're located in Canada.

Would you like to visit our Canada Store?

[NATURE’S WAY CANADA](https://shop.natureswaycanada.ca/?utm_source=nwus&utm_campaign=nwgeo&utm_content=modal) Stay on the USA Store

Cart ()

Cart (0)

Free shipping on US orders $35+ Spend $35.0 to get free shipping!

Loading...

Free shipping on US orders $35+ Spend $35.0 to get free shipping!

### Subtotal

$0.00 USD

Taxes and [shipping](https://naturesway.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout

Update

Check out

 One or more of the items in your cart is a recurring or deferred purchase. By continuing, I agree to the cancellation policy and authorize you to charge my payment method at the prices, frequency and dates listed on this page until my order is fulfilled or I cancel, if permitted.

#### You May Also Like:

##### Loading...

Select Options

Price

Options

   Add to cart Out of stock
